(function(e){function t(t){for(var i,a,c=t[0],s=t[1],d=t[2],u=0,l=[];u<c.length;u++)a=c[u],Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(o,a)&&o[a]&&l.push(o[a][0]),o[a]=0;for(i in s)Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(s,i)&&(e[i]=s[i]);h&&h(t);while(l.length)l.shift()();return r.push.apply(r,d||[]),n()}function n(){for(var e,t=0;t<r.length;t++){for(var n=r[t],i=!0,a=1;a<n.length;a++){var s=n[a];0!==o[s]&&(i=!1)}i&&(r.splice(t--,1),e=c(c.s=n[0]))}return e}var i={},o={app:0},r=[];function a(e){return c.p+"js/"+({}[e]||e)+"."+{"chunk-bee0745c":"41cd9d99"}[e]+".js"}function c(t){if(i[t])return i[t].exports;var n=i[t]={i:t,l:!1,exports:{}};return e[t].call(n.exports,n,n.exports,c),n.l=!0,n.exports}c.e=function(e){var t=[],n=o[e];if(0!==n)if(n)t.push(n[2]);else{var i=new Promise((function(t,i){n=o[e]=[t,i]}));t.push(n[2]=i);var r,s=document.createElement("script");s.charset="utf-8",s.timeout=120,c.nc&&s.setAttribute("nonce",c.nc),s.src=a(e);var d=new Error;r=function(t){s.onerror=s.onload=null,clearTimeout(u);var n=o[e];if(0!==n){if(n){var i=t&&("load"===t.type?"missing":t.type),r=t&&t.target&&t.target.src;d.message="Loading chunk "+e+" failed.\n("+i+": "+r+")",d.name="ChunkLoadError",d.type=i,d.request=r,n[1](d)}o[e]=void 0}};var u=setTimeout((function(){r({type:"timeout",target:s})}),12e4);s.onerror=s.onload=r,document.head.appendChild(s)}return Promise.all(t)},c.m=e,c.c=i,c.d=function(e,t,n){c.o(e,t)||Object.defineProperty(e,t,{enumerable:!0,get:n})},c.r=function(e){"undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})},c.t=function(e,t){if(1&t&&(e=c(e)),8&t)return e;if(4&t&&"object"===typeof e&&e&&e.__esModule)return e;var n=Object.create(null);if(c.r(n),Object.defineProperty(n,"default",{enumerable:!0,value:e}),2&t&&"string"!=typeof e)for(var i in e)c.d(n,i,function(t){return e[t]}.bind(null,i));return n},c.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return c.d(t,"a",t),t},c.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)},c.p="/mousetracking-exp/",c.oe=function(e){throw console.error(e),e};var s=window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[],d=s.push.bind(s);s.push=t,s=s.slice();for(var u=0;u<s.length;u++)t(s[u]);var h=d;r.push([0,"chunk-vendors"]),n()})({0:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n("56d7")},"0c1a":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aicked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"the child with a sweet tooth aicked the",CriticalWord:"aicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the child with a sweet tooth aicked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ploking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is ploking a",CriticalWord:"is ploking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"he is ploking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, he sent his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the hotel front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"at the hotel front desk, he",prefix:"at the hotel front desk, he rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"at the hotel front desk, he rang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the bookworm",prefix:"the bookworm is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the bookworm is managing the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"dolds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the tailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the tailor",prefix:"the tailor dolds a",CriticalWord:"dolds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the tailor dolds a meeting",question:"Does the tailor hold a meeting?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"sikarushes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he sikarushes a",CriticalWord:"sikarushes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"he sikarushes a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, he",prefix:"in the hotel, he is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, he is packing the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"killed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"on the train, he",prefix:"on the train, he killed the",CriticalWord:"killed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, he killed the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the cyclist",prefix:"the cyclist conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the cyclist conceals a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"prlls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the host",prefix:"the host prlls the",CriticalWord:"prlls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the host prlls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"usiled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he usiled the",CriticalWord:"usiled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"he usiled the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"failed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"despite cramming at the last minute, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"despite cramming at the last minute, he",prefix:"despite cramming at the last minute, he failed the",CriticalWord:"failed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"despite cramming at the last minute, he failed the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"fired",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after three months of losses, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"after three months of losses, he",prefix:"after three months of losses, he fired the",CriticalWord:"fired",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"after three months of losses, he fired the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"plants",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the ferryman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the ferryman",prefix:"the ferryman plants the",CriticalWord:"plants",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"the ferryman plants the boat",question:"Does the ferryman row the boat?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"segls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the vendor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"the vendor",prefix:"the vendor segls the",CriticalWord:"segls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"the vendor segls the bottle",question:"Does the vendor seal the bottle?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"random",verb:"gpaled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he gpaled the",CriticalWord:"gpaled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"he gpaled the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"believed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after listening to the speech, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"after listening to the speech, he",prefix:"after listening to the speech, he believed her",CriticalWord:"believed",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"after listening to the speech, he believed her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"killed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a dark alley, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"in a dark alley, he",prefix:"in a dark alley, he killed the",CriticalWord:"killed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"in a dark alley, he killed the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"munches",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the researcher",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"the researcher",prefix:"the researcher munches the",CriticalWord:"munches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"the researcher munches the study",question:"Does the researcher cite the study?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"attacmed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the soldier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"the soldier",prefix:"the soldier attacmed the",CriticalWord:"attacmed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"the soldier attacmed the file",question:"Did the soldier attach the file?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"random",verb:"tenrrons",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he tenrrons a",CriticalWord:"tenrrons",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"he tenrrons a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"bumped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"due to the icy road, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"due to the icy road, he",prefix:"due to the icy road, he bumped the",CriticalWord:"bumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"due to the icy road, he bumped the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"closed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"annoyed by the noise outside, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"annoyed by the noise outside, he",prefix:"annoyed by the noise outside, he closed the",CriticalWord:"closed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"annoyed by the noise outside, he closed the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"mimics",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the sailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the sailor",prefix:"the sailor mimics the",CriticalWord:"mimics",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"the sailor mimics the boat",question:"Does the sailor dock the boat?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jominated",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the chairman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"the chairman",prefix:"the chairman jominated the",CriticalWord:"jominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"the chairman jominated the game",question:"Did the chairman dominate the game?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"random",verb:"iguls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he iguls the",CriticalWord:"iguls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"he iguls the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"drills",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the workshop, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"in the workshop, he",prefix:"in the workshop, he drills the",CriticalWord:"drills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"in the workshop, he drills the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"evaluated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the end of the semester, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"at the end of the semester, he",prefix:"at the end of the semester, he evaluated the",CriticalWord:"evaluated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"at the end of the semester, he evaluated the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"rented",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the kid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"the kid",prefix:"the kid rented the",CriticalWord:"rented",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"the kid rented the puppy",question:"Did the kid tease the puppy?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"pdtched",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the hiker",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"the hiker",prefix:"the hiker pdtched the",CriticalWord:"pdtched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"the hiker pdtched the pants",question:"Did the hiker patch the pants?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"random",verb:"nioled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he nioled his",CriticalWord:"nioled",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"he nioled his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"revived",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the ICU, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"in the ICU, he",prefix:"in the ICU, he revived the",CriticalWord:"revived",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"in the ICU, he revived the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"shipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after receiving the order, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"after receiving the order, he",prefix:"after receiving the order, he shipped the",CriticalWord:"shipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"after receiving the order, he shipped the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"touches",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the customer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"the customer",prefix:"the customer touches the",CriticalWord:"touches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"the customer touches the waiter",question:"Does the customer tip the waiter?",group_id:20,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"0df7":function(e,t,n){},1:function(e,t){},"14d1":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the candy shop, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the candy shop, he",prefix:"in the candy shop, he licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the candy shop, he licked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the photographer",prefix:"the photographer is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the photographer is cooking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"ient",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the gymnast",prefix:"the gymnast ient his",CriticalWord:"ient",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the gymnast ient his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"phrssed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he phrssed the",CriticalWord:"phrssed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"he phrssed the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, he",prefix:"in the library, he is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, he is reading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the fashion studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"at the fashion studio, he",prefix:"at the fashion studio, he folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"at the fashion studio, he folds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the firefighter",prefix:"the firefighter brandishes a",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the firefighter brandishes a person",question:"Did the firefighter save a person?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is ptcking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the gardener",prefix:"the gardener is ptcking the",CriticalWord:"is ptcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the gardener is ptcking the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"opssed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he opssed the",CriticalWord:"opssed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"he opssed the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, he",prefix:"in the park, he rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, he rides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, he",prefix:"on a game show, he polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, he polls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"boiled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the maid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"the maid",prefix:"the maid boiled the",CriticalWord:"boiled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"the maid boiled the clothes",question:"Did the maid dry the clothes?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"yailed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the sender",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"the sender",prefix:"the sender yailed the",CriticalWord:"yailed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"the sender yailed the exam",question:"Did the sender fail the exam?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"parpassed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he parpassed the",CriticalWord:"parpassed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"he parpassed the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rows",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the river, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"on the river, he",prefix:"on the river, he rows the",CriticalWord:"rows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"on the river, he rows the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"sells",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"at the market, he",prefix:"at the market, he sells the",CriticalWord:"sells",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"at the market, he sells the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"vialed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soldier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"the soldier",prefix:"the soldier vialed the",CriticalWord:"vialed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"the soldier vialed the enemy",question:"Did the soldier battle the enemy?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oelieved",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the therapist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"the therapist",prefix:"the therapist oelieved her",CriticalWord:"oelieved",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"the therapist oelieved her claim",question:"Did the therapist believe her claim?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"random",verb:"vícgered",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he vícgered the",CriticalWord:"vícgered",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"he vícgered the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"cites",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when writing a paper, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"when writing a paper, he",prefix:"when writing a paper, he cites the",CriticalWord:"cites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"when writing a paper, he cites the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"attacked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the battlefield, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"in the battlefield, he",prefix:"in the battlefield, he attacked the",CriticalWord:"attacked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"in the battlefield, he attacked the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"cautions",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the investor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"the investor",prefix:"the investor cautions a",CriticalWord:"cautions",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"the investor cautions a fortune",question:"Does the investor earn a fortune?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"fumped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cleaner",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"the cleaner",prefix:"the cleaner fumped the",CriticalWord:"fumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"the cleaner fumped the car",question:"Does the cleaner bump the car?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"random",verb:"afed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he afed the",CriticalWord:"afed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"he afed the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"docks",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the harbor, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"at the harbor, he",prefix:"at the harbor, he docks the",CriticalWord:"docks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"at the harbor, he docks the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"nominated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the board meeting, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"at the board meeting, he",prefix:"at the board meeting, he nominated the",CriticalWord:"nominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"at the board meeting, he nominated the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"hauls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"the player",prefix:"the player hauls the",CriticalWord:"hauls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"the player hauls the card",question:"Does the player draw the card?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"qrills",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the chef",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"the chef",prefix:"the chef qrills the",CriticalWord:"qrills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"the chef qrills the wood",question:"Does the chef drill the wood?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mulussed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he mulussed the",CriticalWord:"mulussed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"he mulussed the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"teased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the dog park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"at the dog park, he",prefix:"at the dog park, he teased the",CriticalWord:"teased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"at the dog park, he teased the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"pitched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a forest clearing, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"in a forest clearing, he",prefix:"in a forest clearing, he pitched the",CriticalWord:"pitched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"in a forest clearing, he pitched the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"fooled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the careless kid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"the careless kid",prefix:"the careless kid fooled his",CriticalWord:"fooled",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"the careless kid fooled his finger",question:"Did the careless kid prick his finger?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"revijed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the editor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"the editor",prefix:"the editor revijed the",CriticalWord:"revijed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"the editor revijed the patient",question:"Did the editor revive the patient?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ednds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he ednds the",CriticalWord:"ednds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"he ednds the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"tipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after enjoying the meal, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"after enjoying the meal, he",prefix:"after enjoying the meal, he tipped the",CriticalWord:"tipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"after enjoying the meal, he tipped the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:8,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},1506:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the soccer player",prefix:"the soccer player licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the soccer player licked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the pastry chef",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the pastry chef",prefix:"the pastry chef is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the pastry chef is cooking a photo",question:"Is the pastry chef taking a photo?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"ient",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he ient his",CriticalWord:"ient",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"he ient his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"phrssed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, he",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, he phrssed the",CriticalWord:"phrssed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, he phrssed the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, he",prefix:"after the manager resigned, he is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, he is reading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the manager",prefix:"the manager folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the manager folds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spectator",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the spectator",prefix:"the spectator brandishes a",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the spectator brandishes a person",question:"Did the spectator save a person?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is ptcking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is ptcking the",CriticalWord:"is ptcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"he is ptcking the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"opssed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"before a road trip, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"before a road trip, he",prefix:"before a road trip, he opssed the",CriticalWord:"opssed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before a road trip, he opssed the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, he",prefix:"on a mission, he rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, he rides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the visitor",prefix:"the visitor polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the visitor polls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"boiled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cook",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"the cook",prefix:"the cook boiled the",CriticalWord:"boiled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"the cook boiled the clothes",question:"Did the cook dry the clothes?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"yailed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he yailed the",CriticalWord:"yailed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"he yailed the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"parpassed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after negotiation failed, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"after negotiation failed, he",prefix:"after negotiation failed, he parpassed the",CriticalWord:"parpassed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"after negotiation failed, he parpassed the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rows",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the field, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"in the field, he",prefix:"in the field, he rows the",CriticalWord:"rows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"in the field, he rows the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"sells",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the brewer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"the brewer",prefix:"the brewer sells the",CriticalWord:"sells",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"the brewer sells the bottle",question:"Does the brewer seal the bottle?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"vialed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the lab technician",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"the lab technician",prefix:"the lab technician vialed the",CriticalWord:"vialed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"the lab technician vialed the enemy",question:"Did the lab technician battle the enemy?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oelieved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he oelieved her",CriticalWord:"oelieved",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"he oelieved her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"random",verb:"vícgered",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after a thoughtful conversation, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"after a thoughtful conversation, he",prefix:"after a thoughtful conversation, he vícgered the",CriticalWord:"vícgered",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"after a thoughtful conversation, he vícgered the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"cites",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the canteen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"in the canteen, he",prefix:"in the canteen, he cites the",CriticalWord:"cites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"in the canteen, he cites the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"attacked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the secretary",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"the secretary",prefix:"the secretary attacked the",CriticalWord:"attacked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"the secretary attacked the file",question:"Did the secretary attach the file?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"cautions",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the policeman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"the policeman",prefix:"the policeman cautions a",CriticalWord:"cautions",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"the policeman cautions a fortune",question:"Does the policeman earn a fortune?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"fumped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he fumped the",CriticalWord:"fumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"he fumped the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"random",verb:"afed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the biology lab, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"in the biology lab, he",prefix:"in the biology lab, he afed the",CriticalWord:"afed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"in the biology lab, he afed the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"docks",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"trying to be playful, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"trying to be playful, he",prefix:"trying to be playful, he docks the",CriticalWord:"docks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"trying to be playful, he docks the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"nominated",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the superstar",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"the superstar",prefix:"the superstar nominated the",CriticalWord:"nominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"the superstar nominated the game",question:"Did the superstar dominate the game?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"hauls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the traveller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"the traveller",prefix:"the traveller hauls the",CriticalWord:"hauls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"the traveller hauls the card",question:"Does the traveller draw the card?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"qrills",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he qrills the",CriticalWord:"qrills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"he qrills the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mulussed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"due to the risk of an explosion, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"due to the risk of an explosion, he",prefix:"due to the risk of an explosion, he mulussed the",CriticalWord:"mulussed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"due to the risk of an explosion, he mulussed the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"teased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the trendy neighborhood, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"in the trendy neighborhood, he",prefix:"in the trendy neighborhood, he teased the",CriticalWord:"teased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"in the trendy neighborhood, he teased the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"pitched",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"the tailor",prefix:"the tailor pitched the",CriticalWord:"pitched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"the tailor pitched the pants",question:"Did the tailor patch the pants?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"fooled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cheeky brother",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"the cheeky brother",prefix:"the cheeky brother fooled his",CriticalWord:"fooled",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"the cheeky brother fooled his finger",question:"Did the cheeky brother prick his finger?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"revijed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he revijed the",CriticalWord:"revijed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"he revijed the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ednds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after staying up too late at a party, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"after staying up too late at a party, he",prefix:"after staying up too late at a party, he ednds the",CriticalWord:"ednds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"after staying up too late at a party, he ednds the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"tipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the checkout counter, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"at the checkout counter, he",prefix:"at the checkout counter, he tipped the",CriticalWord:"tipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"at the checkout counter, he tipped the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:9,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"1cfa":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he aicked the",CriticalWord:"aicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"he aicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ploking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, he",prefix:"in the film studio, he is ploking a",CriticalWord:"is ploking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, he is ploking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, he",prefix:"in the dance studio, he sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, he sent his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the troubadour",prefix:"the troubadour rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the troubadour rang the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the coach",prefix:"the coach is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the coach is managing the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"dolds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he dolds a",CriticalWord:"dolds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"he dolds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"sikarushes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"from the burning house, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"from the burning house, he",prefix:"from the burning house, he sikarushes a",CriticalWord:"sikarushes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"from the burning house, he sikarushes a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the greenhouse, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the greenhouse, he",prefix:"in the greenhouse, he is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the greenhouse, he is packing the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"killed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the driver",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"the driver",prefix:"the driver killed the",CriticalWord:"killed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the driver killed the tank",question:"Is the driver filling the tank?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the spy",prefix:"the spy conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the spy conceals a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"prlls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he prlls the",CriticalWord:"prlls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"he prlls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"usiled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the laundry room, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"in the laundry room, he",prefix:"in the laundry room, he usiled the",CriticalWord:"usiled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"in the laundry room, he usiled the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"failed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the postal service desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"at the postal service desk, he",prefix:"at the postal service desk, he failed the",CriticalWord:"failed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"at the postal service desk, he failed the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"fired",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the legal team",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"the legal team",prefix:"the legal team fired the",CriticalWord:"fired",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"the legal team fired the lawsuit",question:"Did the legal team file the lawsuit?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"plants",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the farmer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the farmer",prefix:"the farmer plants the",CriticalWord:"plants",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"the farmer plants the boat",question:"Does the farmer row the boat?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"segls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he segls the",CriticalWord:"segls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"he segls the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"random",verb:"gpaled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"surrounded by gunfire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"surrounded by gunfire, he",prefix:"surrounded by gunfire, he gpaled the",CriticalWord:"gpaled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"surrounded by gunfire, he gpaled the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"believed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the clinic, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"in the clinic, he",prefix:"in the clinic, he believed her",CriticalWord:"believed",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"in the clinic, he believed her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"killed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the counselor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"the counselor",prefix:"the counselor killed the",CriticalWord:"killed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"the counselor killed the client",question:"Did the counselor bill the client?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"munches",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the hungry man",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"the hungry man",prefix:"the hungry man munches the",CriticalWord:"munches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"the hungry man munches the study",question:"Does the hungry man cite the study?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"attacmed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he attacmed the",CriticalWord:"attacmed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"he attacmed the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"random",verb:"tenrrons",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"because of the good economic situation, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"because of the good economic situation, he",prefix:"because of the good economic situation, he tenrrons a",CriticalWord:"tenrrons",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"because of the good economic situation, he tenrrons a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"bumped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"inside the garbage room, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"inside the garbage room, he",prefix:"inside the garbage room, he bumped the",CriticalWord:"bumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"inside the garbage room, he bumped the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"closed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the scientist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"the scientist",prefix:"the scientist closed the",CriticalWord:"closed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"the scientist closed the gene",question:"Did the scientist clone the gene?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"mimics",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the naughty boy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the naughty boy",prefix:"the naughty boy mimics the",CriticalWord:"mimics",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"the naughty boy mimics the boat",question:"Does the naughty boy dock the boat?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jominated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he jominated the",CriticalWord:"jominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"he jominated the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"random",verb:"iguls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the poker table, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"at the poker table, he",prefix:"at the poker table, he iguls the",CriticalWord:"iguls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"at the poker table, he iguls the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"drills",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the BBQ restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"at the BBQ restaurant, he",prefix:"at the BBQ restaurant, he drills the",CriticalWord:"drills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"at the BBQ restaurant, he drills the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"evaluated",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the security staff",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"the security staff",prefix:"the security staff evaluated the",CriticalWord:"evaluated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"the security staff evaluated the building",question:"Did the security staff evacuate the building?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"rented",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"the tenant",prefix:"the tenant rented the",CriticalWord:"rented",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"the tenant rented the puppy",question:"Did the tenant tease the puppy?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"pdtched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he pdtched the",CriticalWord:"pdtched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"he pdtched the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"random",verb:"nioled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when learning to knit, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"when learning to knit, he",prefix:"when learning to knit, he nioled his",CriticalWord:"nioled",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"when learning to knit, he nioled his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"revived",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after receiving the submission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"after receiving the submission, he",prefix:"after receiving the submission, he revived the",CriticalWord:"revived",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"after receiving the submission, he revived the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"shipped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"the student",prefix:"the student shipped the",CriticalWord:"shipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"the student shipped the class",question:"Does the student skip the class?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"touches",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cashier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"the cashier",prefix:"the cashier touches the",CriticalWord:"touches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"the cashier touches the waiter",question:"Does the cashier tip the waiter?",group_id:16,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},2:function(e,t){},"2bb4":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"the child with a sweet tooth kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the child with a sweet tooth kicked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"he is baking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, he stretched his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"eang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the hotel front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"at the hotel front desk, he",prefix:"at the hotel front desk, he eang the",CriticalWord:"eang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"at the hotel front desk, he eang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is sarrging",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the bookworm",prefix:"the bookworm is sarrging the",CriticalWord:"is sarrging",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the bookworm is sarrging the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the tailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the tailor",prefix:"the tailor holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the tailor holds a meeting",question:"Does the tailor hold a meeting?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he waved a",CriticalWord:"waved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"he waved a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, he",prefix:"in the hotel, he is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, he is watering the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"ailled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"on the train, he",prefix:"on the train, he ailled the",CriticalWord:"ailled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, he ailled the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"defigals",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the cyclist",prefix:"the cyclist defigals a",CriticalWord:"defigals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the cyclist defigals a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the host",prefix:"the host pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the host pulls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"fried",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he fried the",CriticalWord:"fried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"he fried the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"posted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"despite cramming at the last minute, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"despite cramming at the last minute, he",prefix:"despite cramming at the last minute, he posted the",CriticalWord:"posted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"despite cramming at the last minute, he posted the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"fiped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after three months of losses, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"after three months of losses, he",prefix:"after three months of losses, he fiped the",CriticalWord:"fiped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"after three months of losses, he fiped the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hamnts",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the ferryman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the ferryman",prefix:"the ferryman hamnts the",CriticalWord:"hamnts",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"the ferryman hamnts the boat",question:"Does the ferryman row the boat?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"seals",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the vendor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"the vendor",prefix:"the vendor seals the",CriticalWord:"seals",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"the vendor seals the bottle",question:"Does the vendor seal the bottle?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bottled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he bottled the",CriticalWord:"bottled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"he bottled the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"reduced",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after listening to the speech, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"after listening to the speech, he",prefix:"after listening to the speech, he reduced her",CriticalWord:"reduced",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"after listening to the speech, he reduced her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jilled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a dark alley, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"in a dark alley, he",prefix:"in a dark alley, he jilled the",CriticalWord:"jilled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"in a dark alley, he jilled the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"random",verb:"tutches",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the researcher",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"the researcher",prefix:"the researcher tutches the",CriticalWord:"tutches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"the researcher tutches the study",question:"Does the researcher cite the study?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"attached",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the soldier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"the soldier",prefix:"the soldier attached the",CriticalWord:"attached",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"the soldier attached the file",question:"Did the soldier attach the file?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"warns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he warns a",CriticalWord:"warns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"he warns a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"discarded",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"due to the icy road, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"due to the icy road, he",prefix:"due to the icy road, he discarded the",CriticalWord:"discarded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"due to the icy road, he discarded the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"cloled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"annoyed by the noise outside, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"annoyed by the noise outside, he",prefix:"annoyed by the noise outside, he cloled the",CriticalWord:"cloled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"annoyed by the noise outside, he cloled the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"random",verb:"prtics",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the sailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the sailor",prefix:"the sailor prtics the",CriticalWord:"prtics",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"the sailor prtics the boat",question:"Does the sailor dock the boat?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"dominated",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the chairman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"the chairman",prefix:"the chairman dominated the",CriticalWord:"dominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"the chairman dominated the game",question:"Did the chairman dominate the game?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"drags",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he drags the",CriticalWord:"drags",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"he drags the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"broils",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the workshop, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"in the workshop, he",prefix:"in the workshop, he broils the",CriticalWord:"broils",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"in the workshop, he broils the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"evatuated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the end of the semester, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"at the end of the semester, he",prefix:"at the end of the semester, he evatuated the",CriticalWord:"evatuated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"at the end of the semester, he evatuated the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"random",verb:"thnted",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the kid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"the kid",prefix:"the kid thnted the",CriticalWord:"thnted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"the kid thnted the puppy",question:"Did the kid tease the puppy?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"patched",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the hiker",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"the hiker",prefix:"the hiker patched the",CriticalWord:"patched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"the hiker patched the pants",question:"Did the hiker patch the pants?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"tricked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he tricked his",CriticalWord:"tricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"he tricked his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"polished",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the ICU, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"in the ICU, he",prefix:"in the ICU, he polished the",CriticalWord:"polished",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"in the ICU, he polished the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"svipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after receiving the order, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"after receiving the order, he",prefix:"after receiving the order, he svipped the",CriticalWord:"svipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"after receiving the order, he svipped the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"random",verb:"aglches",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the customer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"the customer",prefix:"the customer aglches the",CriticalWord:"aglches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"the customer aglches the waiter",question:"Does the customer tip the waiter?",group_id:5,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"2c35":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the candy shop, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the candy shop, he",prefix:"in the candy shop, he tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the candy shop, he tasted the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is zaking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the photographer",prefix:"the photographer is zaking a",CriticalWord:"is zaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the photographer is zaking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"lunriched",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the gymnast",prefix:"the gymnast lunriched his",CriticalWord:"lunriched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the gymnast lunriched his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"he sang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, he",prefix:"in the library, he is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, he is leading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the fashion studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"at the fashion studio, he",prefix:"at the fashion studio, he creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"at the fashion studio, he creases a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"xaved",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the firefighter",prefix:"the firefighter xaved a",CriticalWord:"xaved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the firefighter xaved a person",question:"Did the firefighter save a person?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is thbering",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the gardener",prefix:"the gardener is thbering the",CriticalWord:"is thbering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the gardener is thbering the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"filled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he filled the",CriticalWord:"filled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"he filled the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, he",prefix:"in the park, he hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, he hides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, he",prefix:"on a game show, he surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, he surveys the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aried",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the maid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"the maid",prefix:"the maid aried the",CriticalWord:"aried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"the maid aried the clothes",question:"Did the maid dry the clothes?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ftsted",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the sender",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"the sender",prefix:"the sender ftsted the",CriticalWord:"ftsted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"the sender ftsted the exam",question:"Did the sender fail the exam?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"filed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he filed the",CriticalWord:"filed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"he filed the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"sows",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the river, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"on the river, he",prefix:"on the river, he sows the",CriticalWord:"sows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"on the river, he sows the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"offers",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"at the market, he",prefix:"at the market, he offers the",CriticalWord:"offers",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"at the market, he offers the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"byttled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soldier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"the soldier",prefix:"the soldier byttled the",CriticalWord:"byttled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"the soldier byttled the enemy",question:"Did the soldier battle the enemy?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"random",verb:"swenced",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the therapist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"the therapist",prefix:"the therapist swenced her",CriticalWord:"swenced",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"the therapist swenced her claim",question:"Did the therapist believe her claim?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"billed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he billed the",CriticalWord:"billed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"he billed the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bites",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when writing a paper, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"when writing a paper, he",prefix:"when writing a paper, he bites the",CriticalWord:"bites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"when writing a paper, he bites the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"struck",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the battlefield, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"in the battlefield, he",prefix:"in the battlefield, he struck the",CriticalWord:"struck",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"in the battlefield, he struck the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"narns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the investor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"the investor",prefix:"the investor narns a",CriticalWord:"narns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"the investor narns a fortune",question:"Does the investor earn a fortune?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"random",verb:"buryarded",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cleaner",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"the cleaner",prefix:"the cleaner buryarded the",CriticalWord:"buryarded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"the cleaner buryarded the car",question:"Does the cleaner bump the car?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"cloned",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he cloned the",CriticalWord:"cloned",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"he cloned the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"mocks",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the harbor, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"at the harbor, he",prefix:"at the harbor, he mocks the",CriticalWord:"mocks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"at the harbor, he mocks the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"recommended",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the board meeting, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"at the board meeting, he",prefix:"at the board meeting, he recommended the",CriticalWord:"recommended",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"at the board meeting, he recommended the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"drazs",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"the player",prefix:"the player drazs the",CriticalWord:"drazs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"the player drazs the card",question:"Does the player draw the card?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"random",verb:"yuails",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the chef",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"the chef",prefix:"the chef yuails the",CriticalWord:"yuails",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"the chef yuails the wood",question:"Does the chef drill the wood?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"evacuated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he evacuated the",CriticalWord:"evacuated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"he evacuated the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"leased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the dog park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"at the dog park, he",prefix:"at the dog park, he leased the",CriticalWord:"leased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"at the dog park, he leased the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"erected",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a forest clearing, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"in a forest clearing, he",prefix:"in a forest clearing, he erected the",CriticalWord:"erected",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"in a forest clearing, he erected the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sricked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the careless kid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"the careless kid",prefix:"the careless kid sricked his",CriticalWord:"sricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"the careless kid sricked his finger",question:"Did the careless kid prick his finger?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"random",verb:"oneished",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the editor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"the editor",prefix:"the editor oneished the",CriticalWord:"oneished",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"the editor oneished the patient",question:"Did the editor revive the patient?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"skipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he skipped the",CriticalWord:"skipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"he skipped the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"tapped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after enjoying the meal, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"after enjoying the meal, he",prefix:"after enjoying the meal, he tapped the",CriticalWord:"tapped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"after enjoying the meal, he tapped the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:13,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},3010:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"artled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the soccer player",prefix:"the soccer player artled the",CriticalWord:"artled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the soccer player artled the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the pastry chef",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the pastry chef",prefix:"the pastry chef is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the pastry chef is taking a photo",question:"Is the pastry chef taking a photo?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"he bent his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, he",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, he pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, he pressed the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is zeading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, he",prefix:"after the manager resigned, he is zeading the",CriticalWord:"is zeading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, he is zeading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"galuses",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the manager",prefix:"the manager galuses a",CriticalWord:"galuses",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the manager galuses a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saved",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spectator",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the spectator",prefix:"the spectator saved a",CriticalWord:"saved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the spectator saved a person",question:"Did the spectator save a person?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"he is picking the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"passed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"before a road trip, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"before a road trip, he",prefix:"before a road trip, he passed the",CriticalWord:"passed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before a road trip, he passed the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"iides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, he",prefix:"on a mission, he iides a",CriticalWord:"iides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, he iides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"phrneys",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the visitor",prefix:"the visitor phrneys the",CriticalWord:"phrneys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the visitor phrneys the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"dried",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cook",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"the cook",prefix:"the cook dried the",CriticalWord:"dried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"the cook dried the clothes",question:"Did the cook dry the clothes?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"mailed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he mailed the",CriticalWord:"mailed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"he mailed the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"dismissed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after negotiation failed, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"after negotiation failed, he",prefix:"after negotiation failed, he dismissed the",CriticalWord:"dismissed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"after negotiation failed, he dismissed the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aows",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the field, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"in the field, he",prefix:"in the field, he aows the",CriticalWord:"aows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"in the field, he aows the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"random",verb:"nokers",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the brewer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"the brewer",prefix:"the brewer nokers the",CriticalWord:"nokers",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"the brewer nokers the bottle",question:"Does the brewer seal the bottle?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"battled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the lab technician",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"the lab technician",prefix:"the lab technician battled the",CriticalWord:"battled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"the lab technician battled the enemy",question:"Did the lab technician battle the enemy?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"relieved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he relieved her",CriticalWord:"relieved",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"he relieved her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"murdered",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after a thoughtful conversation, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"after a thoughtful conversation, he",prefix:"after a thoughtful conversation, he murdered the",CriticalWord:"murdered",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"after a thoughtful conversation, he murdered the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"iites",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the canteen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"in the canteen, he",prefix:"in the canteen, he iites the",CriticalWord:"iites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"in the canteen, he iites the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"random",verb:"kapsed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the secretary",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"the secretary",prefix:"the secretary kapsed the",CriticalWord:"kapsed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"the secretary kapsed the file",question:"Did the secretary attach the file?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"earns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the policeman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"the policeman",prefix:"the policeman earns a",CriticalWord:"earns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"the policeman earns a fortune",question:"Does the policeman earn a fortune?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"dumped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he dumped the",CriticalWord:"dumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"he dumped the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"shut",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the biology lab, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"in the biology lab, he",prefix:"in the biology lab, he shut the",CriticalWord:"shut",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"in the biology lab, he shut the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"vocks",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"trying to be playful, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"trying to be playful, he",prefix:"trying to be playful, he vocks the",CriticalWord:"vocks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"trying to be playful, he vocks the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"random",verb:"prizstanded",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the superstar",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"the superstar",prefix:"the superstar prizstanded the",CriticalWord:"prizstanded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"the superstar prizstanded the game",question:"Did the superstar dominate the game?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"draws",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the traveller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"the traveller",prefix:"the traveller draws the",CriticalWord:"draws",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"the traveller draws the card",question:"Does the traveller draw the card?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"grills",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he grills the",CriticalWord:"grills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"he grills the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"assessed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"due to the risk of an explosion, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"due to the risk of an explosion, he",prefix:"due to the risk of an explosion, he assessed the",CriticalWord:"assessed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"due to the risk of an explosion, he assessed the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"deased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the trendy neighborhood, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"in the trendy neighborhood, he",prefix:"in the trendy neighborhood, he deased the",CriticalWord:"deased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"in the trendy neighborhood, he deased the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jabcted",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"the tailor",prefix:"the tailor jabcted the",CriticalWord:"jabcted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"the tailor jabcted the pants",question:"Did the tailor patch the pants?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pricked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cheeky brother",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"the cheeky brother",prefix:"the cheeky brother pricked his",CriticalWord:"pricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"the cheeky brother pricked his finger",question:"Did the cheeky brother prick his finger?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"revised",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he revised the",CriticalWord:"revised",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"he revised the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"sends",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after staying up too late at a party, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"after staying up too late at a party, he",prefix:"after staying up too late at a party, he sends the",CriticalWord:"sends",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"after staying up too late at a party, he sends the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tnpped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the checkout counter, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"at the checkout counter, he",prefix:"at the checkout counter, he tnpped the",CriticalWord:"tnpped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"at the checkout counter, he tnpped the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:24,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"3c57":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the candy shop, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the candy shop, he",prefix:"in the candy shop, he kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the candy shop, he kicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the photographer",prefix:"the photographer is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the photographer is baking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the gymnast",prefix:"the gymnast stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the gymnast stretched his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"eang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he eang the",CriticalWord:"eang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"he eang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is sarrging",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, he",prefix:"in the library, he is sarrging the",CriticalWord:"is sarrging",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, he is sarrging the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the fashion studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"at the fashion studio, he",prefix:"at the fashion studio, he holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"at the fashion studio, he holds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waved",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the firefighter",prefix:"the firefighter waved a",CriticalWord:"waved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the firefighter waved a person",question:"Did the firefighter save a person?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the gardener",prefix:"the gardener is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the gardener is watering the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"ailled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he ailled the",CriticalWord:"ailled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"he ailled the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"defigals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, he",prefix:"in the park, he defigals a",CriticalWord:"defigals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, he defigals a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, he",prefix:"on a game show, he pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, he pulls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"fried",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the maid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"the maid",prefix:"the maid fried the",CriticalWord:"fried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"the maid fried the clothes",question:"Did the maid dry the clothes?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"posted",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the sender",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"the sender",prefix:"the sender posted the",CriticalWord:"posted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"the sender posted the exam",question:"Did the sender fail the exam?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"fiped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he fiped the",CriticalWord:"fiped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"he fiped the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hamnts",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the river, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"on the river, he",prefix:"on the river, he hamnts the",CriticalWord:"hamnts",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"on the river, he hamnts the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"seals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"at the market, he",prefix:"at the market, he seals the",CriticalWord:"seals",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"at the market, he seals the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bottled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soldier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"the soldier",prefix:"the soldier bottled the",CriticalWord:"bottled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"the soldier bottled the enemy",question:"Did the soldier battle the enemy?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"reduced",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the therapist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"the therapist",prefix:"the therapist reduced her",CriticalWord:"reduced",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"the therapist reduced her claim",question:"Did the therapist believe her claim?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jilled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he jilled the",CriticalWord:"jilled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"he jilled the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"random",verb:"tutches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when writing a paper, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"when writing a paper, he",prefix:"when writing a paper, he tutches the",CriticalWord:"tutches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"when writing a paper, he tutches the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"attached",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the battlefield, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"in the battlefield, he",prefix:"in the battlefield, he attached the",CriticalWord:"attached",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"in the battlefield, he attached the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"warns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the investor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"the investor",prefix:"the investor warns a",CriticalWord:"warns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"the investor warns a fortune",question:"Does the investor earn a fortune?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"discarded",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cleaner",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"the cleaner",prefix:"the cleaner discarded the",CriticalWord:"discarded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"the cleaner discarded the car",question:"Does the cleaner bump the car?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"cloled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he cloled the",CriticalWord:"cloled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"he cloled the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"random",verb:"prtics",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the harbor, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"at the harbor, he",prefix:"at the harbor, he prtics the",CriticalWord:"prtics",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"at the harbor, he prtics the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"dominated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the board meeting, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"at the board meeting, he",prefix:"at the board meeting, he dominated the",CriticalWord:"dominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"at the board meeting, he dominated the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"drags",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"the player",prefix:"the player drags the",CriticalWord:"drags",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"the player drags the card",question:"Does the player draw the card?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"broils",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the chef",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"the chef",prefix:"the chef broils the",CriticalWord:"broils",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"the chef broils the wood",question:"Does the chef drill the wood?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"evatuated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he evatuated the",CriticalWord:"evatuated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"he evatuated the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"random",verb:"thnted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the dog park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"at the dog park, he",prefix:"at the dog park, he thnted the",CriticalWord:"thnted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"at the dog park, he thnted the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"patched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a forest clearing, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"in a forest clearing, he",prefix:"in a forest clearing, he patched the",CriticalWord:"patched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"in a forest clearing, he patched the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"tricked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the careless kid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"the careless kid",prefix:"the careless kid tricked his",CriticalWord:"tricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"the careless kid tricked his finger",question:"Did the careless kid prick his finger?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"polished",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the editor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"the editor",prefix:"the editor polished the",CriticalWord:"polished",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"the editor polished the patient",question:"Did the editor revive the patient?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"svipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he svipped the",CriticalWord:"svipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"he svipped the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"random",verb:"aglches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after enjoying the meal, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"after enjoying the meal, he",prefix:"after enjoying the meal, he aglches the",CriticalWord:"aglches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"after enjoying the meal, he aglches the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:3,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"3c7c":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"he kicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, he",prefix:"in the film studio, he is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, he is baking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, he",prefix:"in the dance studio, he stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, he stretched his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"eang",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the troubadour",prefix:"the troubadour eang the",CriticalWord:"eang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the troubadour eang the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is sarrging",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the coach",prefix:"the coach is sarrging the",CriticalWord:"is sarrging",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the coach is sarrging the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"he holds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"from the burning house, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"from the burning house, he",prefix:"from the burning house, he waved a",CriticalWord:"waved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"from the burning house, he waved a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the greenhouse, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the greenhouse, he",prefix:"in the greenhouse, he is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the greenhouse, he is watering the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"ailled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the driver",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"the driver",prefix:"the driver ailled the",CriticalWord:"ailled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the driver ailled the tank",question:"Is the driver filling the tank?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"defigals",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the spy",prefix:"the spy defigals a",CriticalWord:"defigals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the spy defigals a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"he pulls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"fried",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the laundry room, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"in the laundry room, he",prefix:"in the laundry room, he fried the",CriticalWord:"fried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"in the laundry room, he fried the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"posted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the postal service desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"at the postal service desk, he",prefix:"at the postal service desk, he posted the",CriticalWord:"posted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"at the postal service desk, he posted the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"fiped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the legal team",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"the legal team",prefix:"the legal team fiped the",CriticalWord:"fiped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"the legal team fiped the lawsuit",question:"Did the legal team file the lawsuit?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hamnts",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the farmer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the farmer",prefix:"the farmer hamnts the",CriticalWord:"hamnts",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"the farmer hamnts the boat",question:"Does the farmer row the boat?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"seals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he seals the",CriticalWord:"seals",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"he seals the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bottled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"surrounded by gunfire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"surrounded by gunfire, he",prefix:"surrounded by gunfire, he bottled the",CriticalWord:"bottled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"surrounded by gunfire, he bottled the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"reduced",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the clinic, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"in the clinic, he",prefix:"in the clinic, he reduced her",CriticalWord:"reduced",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"in the clinic, he reduced her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jilled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the counselor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"the counselor",prefix:"the counselor jilled the",CriticalWord:"jilled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"the counselor jilled the client",question:"Did the counselor bill the client?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"random",verb:"tutches",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the hungry man",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"the hungry man",prefix:"the hungry man tutches the",CriticalWord:"tutches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"the hungry man tutches the study",question:"Does the hungry man cite the study?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"attached",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he attached the",CriticalWord:"attached",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"he attached the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"warns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"because of the good economic situation, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"because of the good economic situation, he",prefix:"because of the good economic situation, he warns a",CriticalWord:"warns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"because of the good economic situation, he warns a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"discarded",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"inside the garbage room, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"inside the garbage room, he",prefix:"inside the garbage room, he discarded the",CriticalWord:"discarded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"inside the garbage room, he discarded the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"cloled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the scientist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"the scientist",prefix:"the scientist cloled the",CriticalWord:"cloled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"the scientist cloled the gene",question:"Did the scientist clone the gene?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"random",verb:"prtics",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the naughty boy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the naughty boy",prefix:"the naughty boy prtics the",CriticalWord:"prtics",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"the naughty boy prtics the boat",question:"Does the naughty boy dock the boat?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"dominated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he dominated the",CriticalWord:"dominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"he dominated the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"drags",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the poker table, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"at the poker table, he",prefix:"at the poker table, he drags the",CriticalWord:"drags",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"at the poker table, he drags the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"broils",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the BBQ restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"at the BBQ restaurant, he",prefix:"at the BBQ restaurant, he broils the",CriticalWord:"broils",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"at the BBQ restaurant, he broils the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"evatuated",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the security staff",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"the security staff",prefix:"the security staff evatuated the",CriticalWord:"evatuated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"the security staff evatuated the building",question:"Did the security staff evacuate the building?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"random",verb:"thnted",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"the tenant",prefix:"the tenant thnted the",CriticalWord:"thnted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"the tenant thnted the puppy",question:"Did the tenant tease the puppy?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"patched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he patched the",CriticalWord:"patched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"he patched the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"tricked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when learning to knit, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"when learning to knit, he",prefix:"when learning to knit, he tricked his",CriticalWord:"tricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"when learning to knit, he tricked his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"polished",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after receiving the submission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"after receiving the submission, he",prefix:"after receiving the submission, he polished the",CriticalWord:"polished",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"after receiving the submission, he polished the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"svipped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"the student",prefix:"the student svipped the",CriticalWord:"svipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"the student svipped the class",question:"Does the student skip the class?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"random",verb:"aglches",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cashier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"the cashier",prefix:"the cashier aglches the",CriticalWord:"aglches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"the cashier aglches the waiter",question:"Does the cashier tip the waiter?",group_id:1,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},4149:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"the child with a sweet tooth licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the child with a sweet tooth licked the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"he is cooking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"ient",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he ient his",CriticalWord:"ient",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, he ient his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"phrssed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the hotel front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"at the hotel front desk, he",prefix:"at the hotel front desk, he phrssed the",CriticalWord:"phrssed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"at the hotel front desk, he phrssed the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the bookworm",prefix:"the bookworm is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the bookworm is reading the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the tailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the tailor",prefix:"the tailor folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the tailor folds a meeting",question:"Does the tailor hold a meeting?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he brandishes a",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"he brandishes a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is ptcking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, he",prefix:"in the hotel, he is ptcking the",CriticalWord:"is ptcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, he is ptcking the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"opssed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"on the train, he",prefix:"on the train, he opssed the",CriticalWord:"opssed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, he opssed the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the cyclist",prefix:"the cyclist rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the cyclist rides a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the host",prefix:"the host polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the host polls the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"boiled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he boiled the",CriticalWord:"boiled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"he boiled the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"yailed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"despite cramming at the last minute, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"despite cramming at the last minute, he",prefix:"despite cramming at the last minute, he yailed the",CriticalWord:"yailed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"despite cramming at the last minute, he yailed the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"parpassed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after three months of losses, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"after three months of losses, he",prefix:"after three months of losses, he parpassed the",CriticalWord:"parpassed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"after three months of losses, he parpassed the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rows",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the ferryman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the ferryman",prefix:"the ferryman rows the",CriticalWord:"rows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"the ferryman rows the boat",question:"Does the ferryman row the boat?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"sells",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the vendor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"the vendor",prefix:"the vendor sells the",CriticalWord:"sells",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"the vendor sells the bottle",question:"Does the vendor seal the bottle?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"vialed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he vialed the",CriticalWord:"vialed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"he vialed the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oelieved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after listening to the speech, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"after listening to the speech, he",prefix:"after listening to the speech, he oelieved her",CriticalWord:"oelieved",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"after listening to the speech, he oelieved her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"random",verb:"vícgered",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a dark alley, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"in a dark alley, he",prefix:"in a dark alley, he vícgered the",CriticalWord:"vícgered",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"in a dark alley, he vícgered the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"cites",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the researcher",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"the researcher",prefix:"the researcher cites the",CriticalWord:"cites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"the researcher cites the study",question:"Does the researcher cite the study?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"attacked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the soldier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"the soldier",prefix:"the soldier attacked the",CriticalWord:"attacked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"the soldier attacked the file",question:"Did the soldier attach the file?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"cautions",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he cautions a",CriticalWord:"cautions",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"he cautions a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"fumped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"due to the icy road, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"due to the icy road, he",prefix:"due to the icy road, he fumped the",CriticalWord:"fumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"due to the icy road, he fumped the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"random",verb:"afed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"annoyed by the noise outside, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"annoyed by the noise outside, he",prefix:"annoyed by the noise outside, he afed the",CriticalWord:"afed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"annoyed by the noise outside, he afed the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"docks",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the sailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the sailor",prefix:"the sailor docks the",CriticalWord:"docks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"the sailor docks the boat",question:"Does the sailor dock the boat?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"nominated",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the chairman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"the chairman",prefix:"the chairman nominated the",CriticalWord:"nominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"the chairman nominated the game",question:"Did the chairman dominate the game?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"hauls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he hauls the",CriticalWord:"hauls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"he hauls the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"qrills",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the workshop, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"in the workshop, he",prefix:"in the workshop, he qrills the",CriticalWord:"qrills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"in the workshop, he qrills the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mulussed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the end of the semester, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"at the end of the semester, he",prefix:"at the end of the semester, he mulussed the",CriticalWord:"mulussed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"at the end of the semester, he mulussed the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"teased",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the kid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"the kid",prefix:"the kid teased the",CriticalWord:"teased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"the kid teased the puppy",question:"Did the kid tease the puppy?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"pitched",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the hiker",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"the hiker",prefix:"the hiker pitched the",CriticalWord:"pitched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"the hiker pitched the pants",question:"Did the hiker patch the pants?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"fooled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he fooled his",CriticalWord:"fooled",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"he fooled his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"revijed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the ICU, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"in the ICU, he",prefix:"in the ICU, he revijed the",CriticalWord:"revijed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"in the ICU, he revijed the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ednds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after receiving the order, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"after receiving the order, he",prefix:"after receiving the order, he ednds the",CriticalWord:"ednds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"after receiving the order, he ednds the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"tipped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the customer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"the customer",prefix:"the customer tipped the",CriticalWord:"tipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"the customer tipped the waiter",question:"Does the customer tip the waiter?",group_id:10,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"4cc8":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aicked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the soccer player",prefix:"the soccer player aicked the",CriticalWord:"aicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the soccer player aicked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ploking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the pastry chef",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the pastry chef",prefix:"the pastry chef is ploking a",CriticalWord:"is ploking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the pastry chef is ploking a photo",question:"Is the pastry chef taking a photo?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"he sent his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, he",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, he rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, he rang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, he",prefix:"after the manager resigned, he is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, he is managing the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"dolds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the manager",prefix:"the manager dolds a",CriticalWord:"dolds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the manager dolds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"sikarushes",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spectator",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the spectator",prefix:"the spectator sikarushes a",CriticalWord:"sikarushes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the spectator sikarushes a person",question:"Did the spectator save a person?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"he is packing the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"killed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"before a road trip, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"before a road trip, he",prefix:"before a road trip, he killed the",CriticalWord:"killed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before a road trip, he killed the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, he",prefix:"on a mission, he conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, he conceals a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"prlls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the visitor",prefix:"the visitor prlls the",CriticalWord:"prlls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the visitor prlls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"usiled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cook",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"the cook",prefix:"the cook usiled the",CriticalWord:"usiled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"the cook usiled the clothes",question:"Did the cook dry the clothes?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"failed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he failed the",CriticalWord:"failed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"he failed the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"fired",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after negotiation failed, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"after negotiation failed, he",prefix:"after negotiation failed, he fired the",CriticalWord:"fired",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"after negotiation failed, he fired the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"plants",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the field, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"in the field, he",prefix:"in the field, he plants the",CriticalWord:"plants",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"in the field, he plants the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"segls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the brewer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"the brewer",prefix:"the brewer segls the",CriticalWord:"segls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"the brewer segls the bottle",question:"Does the brewer seal the bottle?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"random",verb:"gpaled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the lab technician",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"the lab technician",prefix:"the lab technician gpaled the",CriticalWord:"gpaled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"the lab technician gpaled the enemy",question:"Did the lab technician battle the enemy?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"believed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he believed her",CriticalWord:"believed",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"he believed her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"killed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after a thoughtful conversation, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"after a thoughtful conversation, he",prefix:"after a thoughtful conversation, he killed the",CriticalWord:"killed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"after a thoughtful conversation, he killed the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"munches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the canteen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"in the canteen, he",prefix:"in the canteen, he munches the",CriticalWord:"munches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"in the canteen, he munches the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"attacmed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the secretary",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"the secretary",prefix:"the secretary attacmed the",CriticalWord:"attacmed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"the secretary attacmed the file",question:"Did the secretary attach the file?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"random",verb:"tenrrons",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the policeman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"the policeman",prefix:"the policeman tenrrons a",CriticalWord:"tenrrons",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"the policeman tenrrons a fortune",question:"Does the policeman earn a fortune?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"bumped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he bumped the",CriticalWord:"bumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"he bumped the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"closed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the biology lab, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"in the biology lab, he",prefix:"in the biology lab, he closed the",CriticalWord:"closed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"in the biology lab, he closed the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"mimics",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"trying to be playful, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"trying to be playful, he",prefix:"trying to be playful, he mimics the",CriticalWord:"mimics",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"trying to be playful, he mimics the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jominated",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the superstar",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"the superstar",prefix:"the superstar jominated the",CriticalWord:"jominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"the superstar jominated the game",question:"Did the superstar dominate the game?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"random",verb:"iguls",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the traveller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"the traveller",prefix:"the traveller iguls the",CriticalWord:"iguls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"the traveller iguls the card",question:"Does the traveller draw the card?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"drills",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he drills the",CriticalWord:"drills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"he drills the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"evaluated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"due to the risk of an explosion, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"due to the risk of an explosion, he",prefix:"due to the risk of an explosion, he evaluated the",CriticalWord:"evaluated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"due to the risk of an explosion, he evaluated the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"rented",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the trendy neighborhood, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"in the trendy neighborhood, he",prefix:"in the trendy neighborhood, he rented the",CriticalWord:"rented",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"in the trendy neighborhood, he rented the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"pdtched",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"the tailor",prefix:"the tailor pdtched the",CriticalWord:"pdtched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"the tailor pdtched the pants",question:"Did the tailor patch the pants?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"random",verb:"nioled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cheeky brother",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"the cheeky brother",prefix:"the cheeky brother nioled his",CriticalWord:"nioled",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"the cheeky brother nioled his finger",question:"Did the cheeky brother prick his finger?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"revived",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he revived the",CriticalWord:"revived",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"he revived the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"shipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after staying up too late at a party, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"after staying up too late at a party, he",prefix:"after staying up too late at a party, he shipped the",CriticalWord:"shipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"after staying up too late at a party, he shipped the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"touches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the checkout counter, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"at the checkout counter, he",prefix:"at the checkout counter, he touches the",CriticalWord:"touches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"at the checkout counter, he touches the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:19,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},5030:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, he",prefix:"on the playground, he aicked the",CriticalWord:"aicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, he aicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ploking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he is ploking a",CriticalWord:"is ploking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, he is ploking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the mailman",prefix:"the mailman sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the mailman sent his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the guest",prefix:"the guest rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the guest rang the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"he is managing the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"dolds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he dolds a",CriticalWord:"dolds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he dolds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"sikarushes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the football game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the football game, he",prefix:"at the football game, he sikarushes a",CriticalWord:"sikarushes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the football game, he sikarushes a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the traveler",prefix:"the traveler is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the traveler is packing the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"killed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"the bored person",prefix:"the bored person killed the",CriticalWord:"killed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the bored person killed the tank",question:"Is the bored person filling the tank?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"he conceals a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"prlls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, he",prefix:"at the entrance, he prlls the",CriticalWord:"prlls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, he prlls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"usiled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he usiled the",CriticalWord:"usiled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"in the kitchen, he usiled the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"failed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the lazy student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"the lazy student",prefix:"the lazy student failed the",CriticalWord:"failed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"the lazy student failed the exam",question:"Did the lazy student fail the exam?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"fired",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the angry boss",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"the angry boss",prefix:"the angry boss fired the",CriticalWord:"fired",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"the angry boss fired the lawsuit",question:"Did the angry boss file the lawsuit?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"plants",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he plants the",CriticalWord:"plants",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"he plants the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"segls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the brewery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"in the brewery, he",prefix:"in the brewery, he segls the",CriticalWord:"segls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"in the brewery, he segls the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"random",verb:"gpaled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the chemistry lab, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"in the chemistry lab, he",prefix:"in the chemistry lab, he gpaled the",CriticalWord:"gpaled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"in the chemistry lab, he gpaled the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"believed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the gullible person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"the gullible person",prefix:"the gullible person believed her",CriticalWord:"believed",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"the gullible person believed her claim",question:"Did the gullible person believe her claim?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"killed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the suspect",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"the suspect",prefix:"the suspect killed the",CriticalWord:"killed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"the suspect killed the client",question:"Did the suspect bill the client?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"munches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he munches the",CriticalWord:"munches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"he munches the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"attacmed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the email, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"in the email, he",prefix:"in the email, he attacmed the",CriticalWord:"attacmed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"in the email, he attacmed the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"random",verb:"tenrrons",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"during the march, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"during the march, he",prefix:"during the march, he tenrrons a",CriticalWord:"tenrrons",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"during the march, he tenrrons a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"bumped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the driver",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"the driver",prefix:"the driver bumped the",CriticalWord:"bumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"the driver bumped the car",question:"Does the driver bump the car?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"closed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the teacher",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"the teacher",prefix:"the teacher closed the",CriticalWord:"closed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"the teacher closed the gene",question:"Did the teacher clone the gene?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"mimics",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he mimics the",CriticalWord:"mimics",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"he mimics the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jominated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the final round of the tournament, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"in the final round of the tournament, he",prefix:"in the final round of the tournament, he jominated the",CriticalWord:"jominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"in the final round of the tournament, he jominated the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"random",verb:"iguls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train platform, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"on the train platform, he",prefix:"on the train platform, he iguls the",CriticalWord:"iguls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"on the train platform, he iguls the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"drills",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the carpenter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"the carpenter",prefix:"the carpenter drills the",CriticalWord:"drills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"the carpenter drills the wood",question:"Does the carpenter drill the wood?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"evaluated",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the professor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"the professor",prefix:"the professor evaluated the",CriticalWord:"evaluated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"the professor evaluated the building",question:"Did the professor evacuate the building?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"rented",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he rented the",CriticalWord:"rented",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"he rented the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"pdtched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"with a sewing machine, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"with a sewing machine, he",prefix:"with a sewing machine, he pdtched the",CriticalWord:"pdtched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"with a sewing machine, he pdtched the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"random",verb:"nioled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a hide-and-seek game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"in a hide-and-seek game, he",prefix:"in a hide-and-seek game, he nioled his",CriticalWord:"nioled",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"in a hide-and-seek game, he nioled his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"revived",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the doctor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"the doctor",prefix:"the doctor revived the",CriticalWord:"revived",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"the doctor revived the patient",question:"Did the doctor revive the patient?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"shipped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the seller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"the seller",prefix:"the seller shipped the",CriticalWord:"shipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"the seller shipped the class",question:"Does the seller skip the class?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"touches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he touches the",CriticalWord:"touches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"he touches the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:17,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},5455:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, he",prefix:"on the playground, he tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, he tasted the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is zaking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he is zaking a",CriticalWord:"is zaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, he is zaking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"lunriched",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the mailman",prefix:"the mailman lunriched his",CriticalWord:"lunriched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the mailman lunriched his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the guest",prefix:"the guest sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the guest sang the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"he is leading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he creases a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"xaved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the football game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the football game, he",prefix:"at the football game, he xaved a",CriticalWord:"xaved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the football game, he xaved a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is thbering",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the traveler",prefix:"the traveler is thbering the",CriticalWord:"is thbering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the traveler is thbering the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"filled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"the bored person",prefix:"the bored person filled the",CriticalWord:"filled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the bored person filled the tank",question:"Is the bored person filling the tank?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"he hides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, he",prefix:"at the entrance, he surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, he surveys the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aried",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he aried the",CriticalWord:"aried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"in the kitchen, he aried the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ftsted",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the lazy student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"the lazy student",prefix:"the lazy student ftsted the",CriticalWord:"ftsted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"the lazy student ftsted the exam",question:"Did the lazy student fail the exam?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"filed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the angry boss",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"the angry boss",prefix:"the angry boss filed the",CriticalWord:"filed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"the angry boss filed the lawsuit",question:"Did the angry boss file the lawsuit?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"sows",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he sows the",CriticalWord:"sows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"he sows the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"offers",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the brewery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"in the brewery, he",prefix:"in the brewery, he offers the",CriticalWord:"offers",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"in the brewery, he offers the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"byttled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the chemistry lab, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"in the chemistry lab, he",prefix:"in the chemistry lab, he byttled the",CriticalWord:"byttled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"in the chemistry lab, he byttled the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"random",verb:"swenced",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the gullible person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"the gullible person",prefix:"the gullible person swenced her",CriticalWord:"swenced",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"the gullible person swenced her claim",question:"Did the gullible person believe her claim?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"billed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the suspect",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"the suspect",prefix:"the suspect billed the",CriticalWord:"billed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"the suspect billed the client",question:"Did the suspect bill the client?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bites",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he bites the",CriticalWord:"bites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"he bites the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"struck",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the email, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"in the email, he",prefix:"in the email, he struck the",CriticalWord:"struck",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"in the email, he struck the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"narns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"during the march, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"during the march, he",prefix:"during the march, he narns a",CriticalWord:"narns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"during the march, he narns a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"random",verb:"buryarded",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the driver",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"the driver",prefix:"the driver buryarded the",CriticalWord:"buryarded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"the driver buryarded the car",question:"Does the driver bump the car?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"cloned",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the teacher",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"the teacher",prefix:"the teacher cloned the",CriticalWord:"cloned",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"the teacher cloned the gene",question:"Did the teacher clone the gene?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"mocks",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he mocks the",CriticalWord:"mocks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"he mocks the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"recommended",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the final round of the tournament, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"in the final round of the tournament, he",prefix:"in the final round of the tournament, he recommended the",CriticalWord:"recommended",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"in the final round of the tournament, he recommended the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"drazs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train platform, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"on the train platform, he",prefix:"on the train platform, he drazs the",CriticalWord:"drazs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"on the train platform, he drazs the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"random",verb:"yuails",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the carpenter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"the carpenter",prefix:"the carpenter yuails the",CriticalWord:"yuails",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"the carpenter yuails the wood",question:"Does the carpenter drill the wood?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"evacuated",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the professor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"the professor",prefix:"the professor evacuated the",CriticalWord:"evacuated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"the professor evacuated the building",question:"Did the professor evacuate the building?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"leased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he leased the",CriticalWord:"leased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"he leased the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"erected",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"with a sewing machine, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"with a sewing machine, he",prefix:"with a sewing machine, he erected the",CriticalWord:"erected",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"with a sewing machine, he erected the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sricked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a hide-and-seek game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"in a hide-and-seek game, he",prefix:"in a hide-and-seek game, he sricked his",CriticalWord:"sricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"in a hide-and-seek game, he sricked his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"random",verb:"oneished",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the doctor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"the doctor",prefix:"the doctor oneished the",CriticalWord:"oneished",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"the doctor oneished the patient",question:"Did the doctor revive the patient?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"skipped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the seller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"the seller",prefix:"the seller skipped the",CriticalWord:"skipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"the seller skipped the class",question:"Does the seller skip the class?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"tapped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he tapped the",CriticalWord:"tapped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"he tapped the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:12,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"56d7":function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var i=n("2b0e"),o=n("7591"),r=n.n(o),a=n("3665"),c=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,n=e._self._c||t;return n("Experiment",{attrs:{title:"Reading Experiment",translate:"no"}},[n("Screen",{staticClass:"instructions",attrs:{title:"Welcome",validations:{SubjectID:{minLength:e.$magpie.v.minLength(2)}}}},[n("div",{staticStyle:{width:"40em",margin:"auto"}},[n("div",{staticStyle:{"background-color":"lightgrey",padding:"10px"}},[n("b",[e._v(" Information About this Study ")])]),n("p",[n("br"),n("b",[e._v("What is being investigated?")]),e._v(" You are being asked to take part in a research study being done at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. This study will help us learn about how people read. It will take you around 20 minutes to complete. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("Who can participate?")]),e._v(" You can participate only if you are an adult native speaker of English. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("What am I supposed to do as a participant?")]),e._v(" If you choose to be in the study, you will use the computer mouse to read sentences in English and answer questions about them. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("What are my rights during participation?")]),e._v(" Your participation in this study is voluntary. If you choose to participate, you may change your mind and leave the study at any time by closing the web page. You do not have to provide reasons. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("What risks and benefits can I expect?")]),e._v(" There are no foreseeable risks for participating in this study. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("Will I be compensated for participating?")]),e._v(" If you complete the experiment, you will be compensated for your time according to the amount specified on Prolific. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v("What data is collected from me and how is it used?")]),e._v(" During this study, we will track the position of your mouse on screen. At the end of the study you will be asked to complete a brief survey. No personally identifying information will be collected. The data from this study may be presented at scientific conferences and published in scientific journals, as well as in online repositories. All data will remain anonymous. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v(" Who reviewed this study? ")]),e._v(" This study's protocol has been approved by the MIT Committee on the Use of Humans as Experimental Subjects. "),n("br"),n("br"),n("b",[e._v(" Contact: ")]),e._v(" Please feel free to contact us anonymously via Prolific Direct Message. "),n("br")]),n("br"),n("div",{staticStyle:{"background-color":"lightgrey",padding:"10px"}},[n("b",[e._v(" Consent Form ")])]),n("br"),e._v(" I, the participant, confirm by clicking the button below: "),n("br"),n("div",{staticStyle:{"padding-left":"30px"}},[e._v(" • I have read and understood the study information above. ")]),n("div",{staticStyle:{"padding-left":"30px"}},[e._v(" • I comply with the inclusion and exclusion criteria for participation described above. ")]),n("div",{staticStyle:{"padding-left":"30px"}},[e._v(" • I have had enough time to decide about my participation. ")]),n("div",{staticStyle:{"padding-left":"30px"}},[e._v(" • I participate in this study voluntarily and consent that my personal data be used as described above. ")]),n("div",{staticStyle:{"padding-left":"30px"}},[e._v(" • I understand that I can stop participating at any moment. ")]),n("br"),n("tr",[n("td",[e._v("Please enter your Prolific ID to continue: ")]),n("td",[n("input",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.$magpie.measurements.SubjectID,expression:"$magpie.measurements.SubjectID"}],staticClass:"obligatory",attrs:{name:"TurkID",type:"text"},domProps:{value:e.$magpie.measurements.SubjectID},on:{input:function(t){t.target.composing||e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"SubjectID",t.target.value)}}})])]),n("tr")]),e.$magpie.measurements.SubjectID&&!e.$magpie.validateMeasurements.SubjectID.$invalid?n("div",[n("br"),e._v(" By clicking on the button below you consent to participating in this study: "),n("button",{on:{click:function(t){e.$magpie.addExpData({SubjectId:e.$magpie.measurements.SubjectID}),e.$magpie.nextScreen()}}},[e._v(" Proceed ")])]):e._e()]),n("InstructionScreen",{attrs:{title:"Instructions"}},[n("p",[e._v(" In this study, you will read sentences. Unlike in normal reading, however, the texts will be blurred. In order to bring the text into focus, move your mouse over it. When you are done reading, click the 'Done Reading' button. ")])]),n("InstructionScreen",{attrs:{title:"Instructions"}},[n("p",[e._v(" Please don't worry about punctuation or capitalization, which are not the focus of this study. ")]),n("p",[e._v(" After reading each sentence, you will be asked a yes-or-no question about the sentence. Indicate your choice by pressing the appropriate button. ")]),n("p",[e._v("Press the button to start the study.")])]),e._l(e.trials,(function(t,i){return[n("Screen",{key:i,staticClass:"main_screen",attrs:{progress:i/e.trials.length}},[n("Slide",[n("form",[n("input",{staticClass:"item_id",attrs:{type:"hidden"},domProps:{value:t.item_id}}),n("input",{staticClass:"experiment_id",attrs:{type:"hidden"},domProps:{value:t.experiment_id}}),n("input",{staticClass:"condition_id",attrs:{type:"hidden"},domProps:{value:t.condition_id}})]),n("div",{staticClass:"oval-cursor"}),[n("div",[e._v("Sentence "+e._s(i+1)+" of "+e._s(e.trials.length))])],e.showFirstDiv?n("div",{staticClass:"readingText",on:{mousemove:e.moveCursor,mouseleave:e.changeBack}},[e._l(t.text.split(" "),(function(t,i){return[n("span",{key:i,attrs:{"data-index":i}},[e._v(" "+e._s(t)+" ")])]}))],2):e._e(),n("div",{staticClass:"blurry-layer",staticStyle:{opacity:"0.3",filter:"blur(5px)",transition:"all 0.3s linear 0s"}},[e._v(" "+e._s(t.text)+" ")]),n("div",{staticStyle:{height:"75px"}}),n("div",[e.showFirstDiv?n("button",{attrs:{disabled:!e.isCursorMoving},on:{click:e.toggleDivs}},[e._v(" Done Reading ")]):e._e()]),e.showFirstDiv?e._e():n("div",{staticClass:"userInput"},[n("p",[e._v(e._s(t.question))]),n("MultipleChoiceInput",{attrs:{response:e.$magpie.measurements.response,options:[t.answer1,t.answer2]},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"response",t)}}})],1),e.$magpie.measurements.response?n("button",{on:{click:function(n){e.toggleDivs();var o=e.$magpie.getAllData()[0].SubjectId;e.$magpie.addTrialData(Object.assign({},{TrialId:i,ItemId:t.item_id,Condition:t.condition_id,Experiment:t.experiment_id,TrialText:t.text,TrialType:"comprehensionQuestion",Question:t.question,Answer1:t.answer1,Answer2:t.answer2,userResponse:e.$magpie.measurements.response},t));var r=e.$magpie.getAllData(),a=r.filter((function(e){return Number(e.ItemId)===t.item_id&&e.Condition===t.condition_id}));a[0].SubjectId=o,e.$magpie.submitResults(e.$magpie.submissionUrl,a),e.$magpie.nextScreen()}}},[e._v(" Next Trial ")]):e._e()],2)],1)]})),n("Screen",[n("p",[e._v("1. Which input device are you using for this experiment?")]),n("MultipleChoiceInput",{attrs:{response:e.$magpie.measurements.device,orientation:"horizontal",options:["Computer Mouse","Computer Trackpad","Other"]},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"device",t)}}}),n("br"),n("br"),n("p",[e._v("2. Which hand are you using during this experiment?")]),n("MultipleChoiceInput",{attrs:{response:e.$magpie.measurements.hand,orientation:"horizontal",options:["Left","Right","Both"]},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"hand",t)}}}),n("br"),n("br"),n("p",[e._v(" What did you think about the experiment? Please describe how hard or easy the task felt, anything you noticed about the sentences, or any other thoughts you have. If anything was confusing or frustrating, please feel free to let us know! ")]),n("TextareaInput",{attrs:{response:e.$magpie.measurements.response},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"response",t)}}}),n("button",{staticStyle:{bottom:"30%",transform:"translate(-50%, -50%)"},on:{click:function(t){return e.$magpie.saveAndNextScreen()}}},[e._v(" Submit ")])],1),n("Screen",[n("p",[e._v(" The next screen will submit your results and display your completion code. ")]),n("button",{staticStyle:{bottom:"30%",transform:"translate(-50%, -50%)"},on:{click:function(t){var n=e.$magpie.getAllData(),i=n[0].SubjectId,o=n[n.length-1],r=[Object.assign({},o,{SubjectId:i})];e.$magpie.submitResults(e.$magpie.submissionUrl,r),e.$magpie.nextScreen()}}},[e._v(" Continue ")])]),n("Screen",{attrs:{title:"Study Complete"}},[n("p",{staticClass:"selectable-text",staticStyle:{"font-size":"24px"}},[e._v("Completion Code:")]),n("p",{staticClass:"selectable-text",staticStyle:{"font-size":"24px"}},[e._v("C101RMLG")])])],2)},s=[],d=n("aed0"),u=n.n(d),h=n("2ef0"),l=n.n(h),_=n("3c7c"),b=n.n(_),p=n("836e"),m=n.n(p),w=n("3c57"),x=n.n(w),v=n("87ca"),g=n.n(v),q=n("2bb4"),f=n.n(q),y=n("d9b0"),j=n.n(y),k=n("5aaa"),D=n.n(k),I=n("14d1"),C=n.n(I),Y=n("1506"),P=n.n(Y),T=n("4149"),N=n.n(T),W=n("8316"),S=n.n(W),z=n("5455"),$=n.n(z),B=n("2c35"),U=n.n(B),Q=n("5ac5"),A=n.n(Q),M=n("b0f8"),L=n.n(M),O=n("1cfa"),E=n.n(O),R=n("5030"),F=n.n(R),H=n("8f6f"),X=n.n(H),G=n("4cc8"),J=n.n(G),K=n("0c1a"),V=n.n(K),Z=n("81b2"),ee=n.n(Z),te=n("b1ea"),ne=n.n(te),ie=n("ba7d"),oe=n.n(ie),re=n("3010"),ae=n.n(re);const ce=new URLSearchParams(window.location.search);console.log(ce);const se=ce.get("LIST_ID")||"1";console.log(se);const de=se.padStart(2,"0"),ue={"01":b.a,"02":m.a,"03":x.a,"04":g.a,"05":f.a,"06":j.a,"07":D.a,"08":C.a,"09":P.a,10:N.a,11:S.a,12:$.a,13:U.a,14:A.a,15:L.a,16:E.a,17:F.a,18:X.a,19:J.a,20:V.a,21:ee.a,22:ne.a,23:oe.a,24:ae.a},he=ue[de]||b.a;var le={name:"App",data(){const e=!1;console.log(he);const t=l.a.shuffle(he).map((e,t)=>({...e,item_id:e["Item"],text:e["sentence"],condition_id:`${e["verb_condition"]}_${e["subject_condition"]}_${e["context_condition"]}_${e["predicate_condition"]}`,experiment_id:"ncprediction",verb_condition:e["verb_condition"],verb:e["verb"],subject_condition:e["subject_condition"],subject:e["subject"],context_condition:e["context_condition"],context:e["context"],predicate_condition:e["predicate_condition"],predicate:e["predicate"],Preamble:e["Preamble"],prefix:e["prefix"],CriticalWord:e["CriticalWord"],intervention_simple:e["intervention_simple"],continuation:e["continuation"],aux:e["aux"],verb_1_o:e["verb_1_o"],question:e["question"],group_id:e["group_id"],answer1:e["answer1"],answer2:e["answer2"],question_delay:e["question_delay"],correct_answer:e["correct_answer"],with_question:e["with_question"],material_id:e["material_id"]})),n=u.a.map((e,t)=>({item_id:e["Item"],text:e["Sentence"],condition_id:"filler",experiment_id:"ncprediction",with_question:e["with_question"],question:e["question"],answer1:e["answer1"],answer2:e["answer2"],correct_answer:e["correct_answer"],question_delay:e["question_delay"]})),i=n.splice(6,5),o=i.concat(l.a.shuffle(t.concat(n)));return console.log(o),{isCursorMoving:!1,trials:o,currentIndex:null,showFirstDiv:!0,mousePosition:{x:0,y:0},userResponse:"",showImages:e}},computed:{console:()=>console,window:()=>window},mounted(){setInterval(this.saveData,50)},methods:{changeBack(){this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").classList.remove("grow"),this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").classList.remove("blank"),this.currentIndex=null},saveData(){if(null!==this.currentIndex){const e=this.$el.querySelector(`span[data-index="${this.currentIndex}"]`);if(e){const t=e.getBoundingClientRect();$magpie.addTrialData({Experiment:this.$el.querySelector(".experiment_id").value,Condition:this.$el.querySelector(".condition_id").value,ItemId:this.$el.querySelector(".item_id").value,Index:this.currentIndex,Word:e.innerHTML,mousePositionX:this.mousePosition.x,mousePositionY:this.mousePosition.y,wordPositionTop:t.top,wordPositionLeft:t.left,wordPositionBottom:t.bottom,wordPositionRight:t.right})}else $magpie.addTrialData({Experiment:this.$el.querySelector(".experiment_id").value,Condition:this.$el.querySelector(".condition_id").value,ItemId:this.$el.querySelector(".item_id").value,Index:this.currentIndex,mousePositionX:this.mousePosition.x,mousePositionY:this.mousePosition.y})}},moveCursor(e){this.isCursorMoving=!0,this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").classList.add("grow");let t=e.clientX,n=e.clientY;const i=document.elementFromPoint(t,n).closest("span");if(i)this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").classList.remove("blank"),this.currentIndex=i.getAttribute("data-index");else{this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").classList.add("blank");const e=document.elementFromPoint(t,n-3).closest("span");this.currentIndex=e?e.getAttribute("data-index"):-1}this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").style.left=t+12+"px",this.$el.querySelector(".oval-cursor").style.top=n-6+"px",this.mousePosition.x=e.clientX,this.mousePosition.y=e.clientY},toggleDivs(){this.showFirstDiv=!this.showFirstDiv,this.isCursorMoving=!1},getScreenDimensions(){return{window_inner_width:window.innerWidth,window_inner_height:window.innerHeight}}}},_e=le,be=(n("8f42"),n("2877")),pe=Object(be["a"])(_e,c,s,!1,null,null,null),me=pe.exports,we={experimentId:"174",serverUrl:"https://noisy-comp-server-311aa565092d.herokuapp.com",socketUrl:"wss://noisy-comp-server-311aa565092d.herokuapp.com/socket",completionUrl:"https://app.prolific.com/submissions/complete?cc=C101RMLG",contactEmail:"thclark@mit.edu",mode:"directLink",language:"en"};i["default"].config.productionTip=!1,i["default"].use(r.a,{prefix:"Canvas"}),i["default"].use(a["a"],we),new i["default"]({render:e=>e(me)}).$mount("#app")},"5aaa":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, he",prefix:"on the playground, he licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, he licked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, he is cooking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"ient",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the mailman",prefix:"the mailman ient his",CriticalWord:"ient",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the mailman ient his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"phrssed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the guest",prefix:"the guest phrssed the",CriticalWord:"phrssed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the guest phrssed the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"he is reading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he folds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the football game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the football game, he",prefix:"at the football game, he brandishes a",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the football game, he brandishes a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is ptcking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the traveler",prefix:"the traveler is ptcking the",CriticalWord:"is ptcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the traveler is ptcking the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"opssed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"the bored person",prefix:"the bored person opssed the",CriticalWord:"opssed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the bored person opssed the tank",question:"Is the bored person filling the tank?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"he rides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, he",prefix:"at the entrance, he polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, he polls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"boiled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he boiled the",CriticalWord:"boiled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"in the kitchen, he boiled the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"yailed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the lazy student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"the lazy student",prefix:"the lazy student yailed the",CriticalWord:"yailed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"the lazy student yailed the exam",question:"Did the lazy student fail the exam?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"parpassed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the angry boss",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"the angry boss",prefix:"the angry boss parpassed the",CriticalWord:"parpassed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"the angry boss parpassed the lawsuit",question:"Did the angry boss file the lawsuit?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rows",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he rows the",CriticalWord:"rows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"he rows the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"sells",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the brewery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"in the brewery, he",prefix:"in the brewery, he sells the",CriticalWord:"sells",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"in the brewery, he sells the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"vialed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the chemistry lab, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"in the chemistry lab, he",prefix:"in the chemistry lab, he vialed the",CriticalWord:"vialed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"in the chemistry lab, he vialed the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oelieved",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the gullible person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"the gullible person",prefix:"the gullible person oelieved her",CriticalWord:"oelieved",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"the gullible person oelieved her claim",question:"Did the gullible person believe her claim?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"random",verb:"vícgered",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the suspect",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"the suspect",prefix:"the suspect vícgered the",CriticalWord:"vícgered",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"the suspect vícgered the client",question:"Did the suspect bill the client?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"cites",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he cites the",CriticalWord:"cites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"he cites the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"attacked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the email, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"in the email, he",prefix:"in the email, he attacked the",CriticalWord:"attacked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"in the email, he attacked the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"cautions",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"during the march, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"during the march, he",prefix:"during the march, he cautions a",CriticalWord:"cautions",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"during the march, he cautions a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"fumped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the driver",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"the driver",prefix:"the driver fumped the",CriticalWord:"fumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"the driver fumped the car",question:"Does the driver bump the car?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"random",verb:"afed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the teacher",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"the teacher",prefix:"the teacher afed the",CriticalWord:"afed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"the teacher afed the gene",question:"Did the teacher clone the gene?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"docks",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he docks the",CriticalWord:"docks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"he docks the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"nominated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the final round of the tournament, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"in the final round of the tournament, he",prefix:"in the final round of the tournament, he nominated the",CriticalWord:"nominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"in the final round of the tournament, he nominated the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"hauls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train platform, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"on the train platform, he",prefix:"on the train platform, he hauls the",CriticalWord:"hauls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"on the train platform, he hauls the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"qrills",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the carpenter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"the carpenter",prefix:"the carpenter qrills the",CriticalWord:"qrills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"the carpenter qrills the wood",question:"Does the carpenter drill the wood?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mulussed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the professor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"the professor",prefix:"the professor mulussed the",CriticalWord:"mulussed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"the professor mulussed the building",question:"Did the professor evacuate the building?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"teased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he teased the",CriticalWord:"teased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"he teased the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"pitched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"with a sewing machine, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"with a sewing machine, he",prefix:"with a sewing machine, he pitched the",CriticalWord:"pitched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"with a sewing machine, he pitched the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"fooled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a hide-and-seek game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"in a hide-and-seek game, he",prefix:"in a hide-and-seek game, he fooled his",CriticalWord:"fooled",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"in a hide-and-seek game, he fooled his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"revijed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the doctor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"the doctor",prefix:"the doctor revijed the",CriticalWord:"revijed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"the doctor revijed the patient",question:"Did the doctor revive the patient?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ednds",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the seller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"the seller",prefix:"the seller ednds the",CriticalWord:"ednds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"the seller ednds the class",question:"Does the seller skip the class?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"tipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he tipped the",CriticalWord:"tipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"he tipped the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:7,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"5ac5":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the soccer player",prefix:"the soccer player tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the soccer player tasted the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is zaking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the pastry chef",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the pastry chef",prefix:"the pastry chef is zaking a",CriticalWord:"is zaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the pastry chef is zaking a photo",question:"Is the pastry chef taking a photo?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"lunriched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he lunriched his",CriticalWord:"lunriched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"he lunriched his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, he",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, he sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, he sang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, he",prefix:"after the manager resigned, he is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, he is leading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the manager",prefix:"the manager creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the manager creases a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"xaved",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spectator",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the spectator",prefix:"the spectator xaved a",CriticalWord:"xaved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the spectator xaved a person",question:"Did the spectator save a person?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is thbering",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is thbering the",CriticalWord:"is thbering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"he is thbering the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"filled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"before a road trip, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"before a road trip, he",prefix:"before a road trip, he filled the",CriticalWord:"filled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before a road trip, he filled the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, he",prefix:"on a mission, he hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, he hides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the visitor",prefix:"the visitor surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the visitor surveys the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aried",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cook",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"the cook",prefix:"the cook aried the",CriticalWord:"aried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"the cook aried the clothes",question:"Did the cook dry the clothes?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ftsted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he ftsted the",CriticalWord:"ftsted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"he ftsted the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"filed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after negotiation failed, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"after negotiation failed, he",prefix:"after negotiation failed, he filed the",CriticalWord:"filed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"after negotiation failed, he filed the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"sows",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the field, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"in the field, he",prefix:"in the field, he sows the",CriticalWord:"sows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"in the field, he sows the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"offers",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the brewer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"the brewer",prefix:"the brewer offers the",CriticalWord:"offers",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"the brewer offers the bottle",question:"Does the brewer seal the bottle?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"byttled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the lab technician",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"the lab technician",prefix:"the lab technician byttled the",CriticalWord:"byttled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"the lab technician byttled the enemy",question:"Did the lab technician battle the enemy?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"random",verb:"swenced",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he swenced her",CriticalWord:"swenced",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"he swenced her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"billed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after a thoughtful conversation, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"after a thoughtful conversation, he",prefix:"after a thoughtful conversation, he billed the",CriticalWord:"billed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"after a thoughtful conversation, he billed the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bites",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the canteen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"in the canteen, he",prefix:"in the canteen, he bites the",CriticalWord:"bites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"in the canteen, he bites the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"struck",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the secretary",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"the secretary",prefix:"the secretary struck the",CriticalWord:"struck",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"the secretary struck the file",question:"Did the secretary attach the file?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"narns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the policeman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"the policeman",prefix:"the policeman narns a",CriticalWord:"narns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"the policeman narns a fortune",question:"Does the policeman earn a fortune?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"random",verb:"buryarded",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he buryarded the",CriticalWord:"buryarded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"he buryarded the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"cloned",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the biology lab, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"in the biology lab, he",prefix:"in the biology lab, he cloned the",CriticalWord:"cloned",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"in the biology lab, he cloned the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"mocks",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"trying to be playful, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"trying to be playful, he",prefix:"trying to be playful, he mocks the",CriticalWord:"mocks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"trying to be playful, he mocks the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"recommended",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the superstar",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"the superstar",prefix:"the superstar recommended the",CriticalWord:"recommended",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"the superstar recommended the game",question:"Did the superstar dominate the game?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"drazs",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the traveller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"the traveller",prefix:"the traveller drazs the",CriticalWord:"drazs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"the traveller drazs the card",question:"Does the traveller draw the card?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"random",verb:"yuails",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he yuails the",CriticalWord:"yuails",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"he yuails the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"evacuated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"due to the risk of an explosion, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"due to the risk of an explosion, he",prefix:"due to the risk of an explosion, he evacuated the",CriticalWord:"evacuated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"due to the risk of an explosion, he evacuated the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"leased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the trendy neighborhood, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"in the trendy neighborhood, he",prefix:"in the trendy neighborhood, he leased the",CriticalWord:"leased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"in the trendy neighborhood, he leased the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"erected",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"the tailor",prefix:"the tailor erected the",CriticalWord:"erected",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"the tailor erected the pants",question:"Did the tailor patch the pants?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sricked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cheeky brother",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"the cheeky brother",prefix:"the cheeky brother sricked his",CriticalWord:"sricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"the cheeky brother sricked his finger",question:"Did the cheeky brother prick his finger?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"random",verb:"oneished",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he oneished the",CriticalWord:"oneished",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"he oneished the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"skipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after staying up too late at a party, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"after staying up too late at a party, he",prefix:"after staying up too late at a party, he skipped the",CriticalWord:"skipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"after staying up too late at a party, he skipped the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"tapped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the checkout counter, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"at the checkout counter, he",prefix:"at the checkout counter, he tapped the",CriticalWord:"tapped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"at the checkout counter, he tapped the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:14,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"81b2":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"artled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he artled the",CriticalWord:"artled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"he artled the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, he",prefix:"in the film studio, he is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, he is taking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, he",prefix:"in the dance studio, he bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, he bent his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the troubadour",prefix:"the troubadour pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the troubadour pressed the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is zeading",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the coach",prefix:"the coach is zeading the",CriticalWord:"is zeading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the coach is zeading the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"galuses",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he galuses a",CriticalWord:"galuses",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"he galuses a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"from the burning house, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"from the burning house, he",prefix:"from the burning house, he saved a",CriticalWord:"saved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"from the burning house, he saved a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the greenhouse, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the greenhouse, he",prefix:"in the greenhouse, he is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the greenhouse, he is picking the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"passed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the driver",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"the driver",prefix:"the driver passed the",CriticalWord:"passed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the driver passed the tank",question:"Is the driver filling the tank?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"iides",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the spy",prefix:"the spy iides a",CriticalWord:"iides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the spy iides a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"phrneys",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he phrneys the",CriticalWord:"phrneys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"he phrneys the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"dried",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the laundry room, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"in the laundry room, he",prefix:"in the laundry room, he dried the",CriticalWord:"dried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"in the laundry room, he dried the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"mailed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the postal service desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"at the postal service desk, he",prefix:"at the postal service desk, he mailed the",CriticalWord:"mailed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"at the postal service desk, he mailed the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"dismissed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the legal team",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"the legal team",prefix:"the legal team dismissed the",CriticalWord:"dismissed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"the legal team dismissed the lawsuit",question:"Did the legal team file the lawsuit?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aows",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the farmer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the farmer",prefix:"the farmer aows the",CriticalWord:"aows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"the farmer aows the boat",question:"Does the farmer row the boat?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"random",verb:"nokers",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he nokers the",CriticalWord:"nokers",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"he nokers the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"battled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"surrounded by gunfire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"surrounded by gunfire, he",prefix:"surrounded by gunfire, he battled the",CriticalWord:"battled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"surrounded by gunfire, he battled the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"relieved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the clinic, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"in the clinic, he",prefix:"in the clinic, he relieved her",CriticalWord:"relieved",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"in the clinic, he relieved her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"murdered",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the counselor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"the counselor",prefix:"the counselor murdered the",CriticalWord:"murdered",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"the counselor murdered the client",question:"Did the counselor bill the client?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"iites",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the hungry man",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"the hungry man",prefix:"the hungry man iites the",CriticalWord:"iites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"the hungry man iites the study",question:"Does the hungry man cite the study?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"random",verb:"kapsed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he kapsed the",CriticalWord:"kapsed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"he kapsed the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"earns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"because of the good economic situation, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"because of the good economic situation, he",prefix:"because of the good economic situation, he earns a",CriticalWord:"earns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"because of the good economic situation, he earns a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"dumped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"inside the garbage room, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"inside the garbage room, he",prefix:"inside the garbage room, he dumped the",CriticalWord:"dumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"inside the garbage room, he dumped the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"shut",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the scientist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"the scientist",prefix:"the scientist shut the",CriticalWord:"shut",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"the scientist shut the gene",question:"Did the scientist clone the gene?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"vocks",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the naughty boy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the naughty boy",prefix:"the naughty boy vocks the",CriticalWord:"vocks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"the naughty boy vocks the boat",question:"Does the naughty boy dock the boat?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"random",verb:"prizstanded",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he prizstanded the",CriticalWord:"prizstanded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"he prizstanded the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"draws",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the poker table, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"at the poker table, he",prefix:"at the poker table, he draws the",CriticalWord:"draws",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"at the poker table, he draws the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"grills",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the BBQ restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"at the BBQ restaurant, he",prefix:"at the BBQ restaurant, he grills the",CriticalWord:"grills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"at the BBQ restaurant, he grills the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"assessed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the security staff",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"the security staff",prefix:"the security staff assessed the",CriticalWord:"assessed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"the security staff assessed the building",question:"Did the security staff evacuate the building?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"deased",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"the tenant",prefix:"the tenant deased the",CriticalWord:"deased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"the tenant deased the puppy",question:"Did the tenant tease the puppy?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jabcted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he jabcted the",CriticalWord:"jabcted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"he jabcted the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pricked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when learning to knit, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"when learning to knit, he",prefix:"when learning to knit, he pricked his",CriticalWord:"pricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"when learning to knit, he pricked his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"revised",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after receiving the submission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"after receiving the submission, he",prefix:"after receiving the submission, he revised the",CriticalWord:"revised",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"after receiving the submission, he revised the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"sends",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"the student",prefix:"the student sends the",CriticalWord:"sends",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"the student sends the class",question:"Does the student skip the class?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tnpped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cashier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"the cashier",prefix:"the cashier tnpped the",CriticalWord:"tnpped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"the cashier tnpped the waiter",question:"Does the cashier tip the waiter?",group_id:21,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},8316:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"he tasted the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is zaking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, he",prefix:"in the film studio, he is zaking a",CriticalWord:"is zaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, he is zaking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"lunriched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, he",prefix:"in the dance studio, he lunriched his",CriticalWord:"lunriched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, he lunriched his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the troubadour",prefix:"the troubadour sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the troubadour sang the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the coach",prefix:"the coach is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the coach is leading the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"he creases a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"xaved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"from the burning house, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"from the burning house, he",prefix:"from the burning house, he xaved a",CriticalWord:"xaved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"from the burning house, he xaved a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is thbering",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the greenhouse, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the greenhouse, he",prefix:"in the greenhouse, he is thbering the",CriticalWord:"is thbering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the greenhouse, he is thbering the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"filled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the driver",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"the driver",prefix:"the driver filled the",CriticalWord:"filled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the driver filled the tank",question:"Is the driver filling the tank?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the spy",prefix:"the spy hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the spy hides a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"he surveys the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aried",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the laundry room, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"in the laundry room, he",prefix:"in the laundry room, he aried the",CriticalWord:"aried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"in the laundry room, he aried the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ftsted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the postal service desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"at the postal service desk, he",prefix:"at the postal service desk, he ftsted the",CriticalWord:"ftsted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"at the postal service desk, he ftsted the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"filed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the legal team",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"the legal team",prefix:"the legal team filed the",CriticalWord:"filed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"the legal team filed the lawsuit",question:"Did the legal team file the lawsuit?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"sows",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the farmer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the farmer",prefix:"the farmer sows the",CriticalWord:"sows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"the farmer sows the boat",question:"Does the farmer row the boat?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"offers",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he offers the",CriticalWord:"offers",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"he offers the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"byttled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"surrounded by gunfire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"surrounded by gunfire, he",prefix:"surrounded by gunfire, he byttled the",CriticalWord:"byttled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"surrounded by gunfire, he byttled the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"random",verb:"swenced",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the clinic, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"in the clinic, he",prefix:"in the clinic, he swenced her",CriticalWord:"swenced",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"in the clinic, he swenced her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"billed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the counselor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"the counselor",prefix:"the counselor billed the",CriticalWord:"billed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"the counselor billed the client",question:"Did the counselor bill the client?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bites",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the hungry man",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"the hungry man",prefix:"the hungry man bites the",CriticalWord:"bites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"the hungry man bites the study",question:"Does the hungry man cite the study?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"struck",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he struck the",CriticalWord:"struck",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"he struck the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"narns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"because of the good economic situation, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"because of the good economic situation, he",prefix:"because of the good economic situation, he narns a",CriticalWord:"narns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"because of the good economic situation, he narns a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"random",verb:"buryarded",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"inside the garbage room, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"inside the garbage room, he",prefix:"inside the garbage room, he buryarded the",CriticalWord:"buryarded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"inside the garbage room, he buryarded the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"cloned",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the scientist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"the scientist",prefix:"the scientist cloned the",CriticalWord:"cloned",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"the scientist cloned the gene",question:"Did the scientist clone the gene?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"mocks",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the naughty boy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the naughty boy",prefix:"the naughty boy mocks the",CriticalWord:"mocks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"the naughty boy mocks the boat",question:"Does the naughty boy dock the boat?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"recommended",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he recommended the",CriticalWord:"recommended",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"he recommended the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"drazs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the poker table, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"at the poker table, he",prefix:"at the poker table, he drazs the",CriticalWord:"drazs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"at the poker table, he drazs the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"random",verb:"yuails",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the BBQ restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"at the BBQ restaurant, he",prefix:"at the BBQ restaurant, he yuails the",CriticalWord:"yuails",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"at the BBQ restaurant, he yuails the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"evacuated",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the security staff",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"the security staff",prefix:"the security staff evacuated the",CriticalWord:"evacuated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"the security staff evacuated the building",question:"Did the security staff evacuate the building?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"leased",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"the tenant",prefix:"the tenant leased the",CriticalWord:"leased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"the tenant leased the puppy",question:"Did the tenant tease the puppy?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"erected",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he erected the",CriticalWord:"erected",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"he erected the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sricked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when learning to knit, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"when learning to knit, he",prefix:"when learning to knit, he sricked his",CriticalWord:"sricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"when learning to knit, he sricked his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"random",verb:"oneished",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after receiving the submission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"after receiving the submission, he",prefix:"after receiving the submission, he oneished the",CriticalWord:"oneished",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"after receiving the submission, he oneished the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"skipped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"the student",prefix:"the student skipped the",CriticalWord:"skipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"the student skipped the class",question:"Does the student skip the class?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"tapped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cashier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"the cashier",prefix:"the cashier tapped the",CriticalWord:"tapped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"the cashier tapped the waiter",question:"Does the cashier tip the waiter?",group_id:11,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"836e":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, he",prefix:"on the playground, he kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, he kicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, he is baking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the mailman",prefix:"the mailman stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the mailman stretched his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"eang",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the guest",prefix:"the guest eang the",CriticalWord:"eang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the guest eang the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is sarrging",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is sarrging the",CriticalWord:"is sarrging",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"he is sarrging the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he holds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the football game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the football game, he",prefix:"at the football game, he waved a",CriticalWord:"waved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the football game, he waved a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the traveler",prefix:"the traveler is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the traveler is watering the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"ailled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"the bored person",prefix:"the bored person ailled the",CriticalWord:"ailled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the bored person ailled the tank",question:"Is the bored person filling the tank?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"defigals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he defigals a",CriticalWord:"defigals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"he defigals a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, he",prefix:"at the entrance, he pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, he pulls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"fried",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he fried the",CriticalWord:"fried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"in the kitchen, he fried the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"posted",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the lazy student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"the lazy student",prefix:"the lazy student posted the",CriticalWord:"posted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"the lazy student posted the exam",question:"Did the lazy student fail the exam?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"fiped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the angry boss",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"the angry boss",prefix:"the angry boss fiped the",CriticalWord:"fiped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"the angry boss fiped the lawsuit",question:"Did the angry boss file the lawsuit?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hamnts",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he hamnts the",CriticalWord:"hamnts",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"he hamnts the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"seals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the brewery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"in the brewery, he",prefix:"in the brewery, he seals the",CriticalWord:"seals",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"in the brewery, he seals the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bottled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the chemistry lab, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"in the chemistry lab, he",prefix:"in the chemistry lab, he bottled the",CriticalWord:"bottled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"in the chemistry lab, he bottled the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"reduced",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the gullible person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"the gullible person",prefix:"the gullible person reduced her",CriticalWord:"reduced",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"the gullible person reduced her claim",question:"Did the gullible person believe her claim?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jilled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the suspect",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"the suspect",prefix:"the suspect jilled the",CriticalWord:"jilled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"the suspect jilled the client",question:"Did the suspect bill the client?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"random",verb:"tutches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he tutches the",CriticalWord:"tutches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"he tutches the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"attached",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the email, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"in the email, he",prefix:"in the email, he attached the",CriticalWord:"attached",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"in the email, he attached the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"warns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"during the march, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"during the march, he",prefix:"during the march, he warns a",CriticalWord:"warns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"during the march, he warns a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"discarded",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the driver",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"the driver",prefix:"the driver discarded the",CriticalWord:"discarded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"the driver discarded the car",question:"Does the driver bump the car?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"cloled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the teacher",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"the teacher",prefix:"the teacher cloled the",CriticalWord:"cloled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"the teacher cloled the gene",question:"Did the teacher clone the gene?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"random",verb:"prtics",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he prtics the",CriticalWord:"prtics",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"he prtics the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"dominated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the final round of the tournament, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"in the final round of the tournament, he",prefix:"in the final round of the tournament, he dominated the",CriticalWord:"dominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"in the final round of the tournament, he dominated the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"drags",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train platform, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"on the train platform, he",prefix:"on the train platform, he drags the",CriticalWord:"drags",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"on the train platform, he drags the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"broils",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the carpenter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"the carpenter",prefix:"the carpenter broils the",CriticalWord:"broils",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"the carpenter broils the wood",question:"Does the carpenter drill the wood?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"evatuated",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the professor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"the professor",prefix:"the professor evatuated the",CriticalWord:"evatuated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"the professor evatuated the building",question:"Did the professor evacuate the building?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"random",verb:"thnted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he thnted the",CriticalWord:"thnted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"he thnted the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"patched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"with a sewing machine, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"with a sewing machine, he",prefix:"with a sewing machine, he patched the",CriticalWord:"patched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"with a sewing machine, he patched the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"tricked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a hide-and-seek game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"in a hide-and-seek game, he",prefix:"in a hide-and-seek game, he tricked his",CriticalWord:"tricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"in a hide-and-seek game, he tricked his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"polished",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the doctor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"the doctor",prefix:"the doctor polished the",CriticalWord:"polished",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"the doctor polished the patient",question:"Did the doctor revive the patient?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"svipped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the seller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"the seller",prefix:"the seller svipped the",CriticalWord:"svipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"the seller svipped the class",question:"Does the seller skip the class?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"random",verb:"aglches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he aglches the",CriticalWord:"aglches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"he aglches the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:2,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"87ca":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"kicked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soccer player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the soccer player",prefix:"the soccer player kicked the",CriticalWord:"kicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the soccer player kicked the ball",question:"Did the soccer player kick the ball?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is baking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the pastry chef",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the pastry chef",prefix:"the pastry chef is baking a",CriticalWord:"is baking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the pastry chef is baking a photo",question:"Is the pastry chef taking a photo?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"stretched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he stretched his",CriticalWord:"stretched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"he stretched his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"eang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the stage in the tavern, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"on the stage in the tavern, he",prefix:"on the stage in the tavern, he eang the",CriticalWord:"eang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"on the stage in the tavern, he eang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is sarrging",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after the manager resigned, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"after the manager resigned, he",prefix:"after the manager resigned, he is sarrging the",CriticalWord:"is sarrging",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"after the manager resigned, he is sarrging the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"holds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the manager",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the manager",prefix:"the manager holds a",CriticalWord:"holds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the manager holds a meeting",question:"Does the manager hold a meeting?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"waved",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spectator",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the spectator",prefix:"the spectator waved a",CriticalWord:"waved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the spectator waved a person",question:"Did the spectator save a person?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is watering",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is watering the",CriticalWord:"is watering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"he is watering the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"ailled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"before a road trip, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"before a road trip, he",prefix:"before a road trip, he ailled the",CriticalWord:"ailled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"before a road trip, he ailled the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"random",verb:"defigals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a mission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"on a mission, he",prefix:"on a mission, he defigals a",CriticalWord:"defigals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"on a mission, he defigals a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pulls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the visitor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the visitor",prefix:"the visitor pulls the",CriticalWord:"pulls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the visitor pulls the door",question:"Does the visitor pull the door?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"fried",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cook",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"the cook",prefix:"the cook fried the",CriticalWord:"fried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"the cook fried the clothes",question:"Did the cook dry the clothes?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"posted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he posted the",CriticalWord:"posted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"he posted the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"fiped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after negotiation failed, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"after negotiation failed, he",prefix:"after negotiation failed, he fiped the",CriticalWord:"fiped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"after negotiation failed, he fiped the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"random",verb:"hamnts",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the field, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"in the field, he",prefix:"in the field, he hamnts the",CriticalWord:"hamnts",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"in the field, he hamnts the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"seals",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the brewer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"the brewer",prefix:"the brewer seals the",CriticalWord:"seals",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"the brewer seals the bottle",question:"Does the brewer seal the bottle?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bottled",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the lab technician",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"the lab technician",prefix:"the lab technician bottled the",CriticalWord:"bottled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"the lab technician bottled the enemy",question:"Did the lab technician battle the enemy?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"reduced",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he reduced her",CriticalWord:"reduced",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"he reduced her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jilled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after a thoughtful conversation, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"after a thoughtful conversation, he",prefix:"after a thoughtful conversation, he jilled the",CriticalWord:"jilled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"after a thoughtful conversation, he jilled the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"random",verb:"tutches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the canteen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"in the canteen, he",prefix:"in the canteen, he tutches the",CriticalWord:"tutches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"in the canteen, he tutches the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"attached",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the secretary",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"the secretary",prefix:"the secretary attached the",CriticalWord:"attached",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"the secretary attached the file",question:"Did the secretary attach the file?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"warns",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the policeman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"the policeman",prefix:"the policeman warns a",CriticalWord:"warns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"the policeman warns a fortune",question:"Does the policeman earn a fortune?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"discarded",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he discarded the",CriticalWord:"discarded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"he discarded the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"cloled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the biology lab, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"in the biology lab, he",prefix:"in the biology lab, he cloled the",CriticalWord:"cloled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"in the biology lab, he cloled the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"random",verb:"prtics",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"trying to be playful, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"trying to be playful, he",prefix:"trying to be playful, he prtics the",CriticalWord:"prtics",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"trying to be playful, he prtics the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"dominated",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the superstar",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"the superstar",prefix:"the superstar dominated the",CriticalWord:"dominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"the superstar dominated the game",question:"Did the superstar dominate the game?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"drags",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the traveller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"the traveller",prefix:"the traveller drags the",CriticalWord:"drags",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"the traveller drags the card",question:"Does the traveller draw the card?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"broils",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he broils the",CriticalWord:"broils",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"he broils the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"evatuated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"due to the risk of an explosion, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"due to the risk of an explosion, he",prefix:"due to the risk of an explosion, he evatuated the",CriticalWord:"evatuated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"due to the risk of an explosion, he evatuated the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"random",verb:"thnted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the trendy neighborhood, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"in the trendy neighborhood, he",prefix:"in the trendy neighborhood, he thnted the",CriticalWord:"thnted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"in the trendy neighborhood, he thnted the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"patched",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the tailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"the tailor",prefix:"the tailor patched the",CriticalWord:"patched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"the tailor patched the pants",question:"Did the tailor patch the pants?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"tricked",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cheeky brother",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"the cheeky brother",prefix:"the cheeky brother tricked his",CriticalWord:"tricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"the cheeky brother tricked his finger",question:"Did the cheeky brother prick his finger?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"polished",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he polished the",CriticalWord:"polished",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"he polished the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"svipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after staying up too late at a party, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"after staying up too late at a party, he",prefix:"after staying up too late at a party, he svipped the",CriticalWord:"svipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"after staying up too late at a party, he svipped the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"random",verb:"aglches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the checkout counter, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"at the checkout counter, he",prefix:"at the checkout counter, he aglches the",CriticalWord:"aglches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"at the checkout counter, he aglches the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:4,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},"8f42":function(e,t,n){"use strict";n("0df7")},"8f6f":function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aicked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the candy shop, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the candy shop, he",prefix:"in the candy shop, he aicked the",CriticalWord:"aicked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the candy shop, he aicked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is ploking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the photographer",prefix:"the photographer is ploking a",CriticalWord:"is ploking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the photographer is ploking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sent",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the gymnast",prefix:"the gymnast sent his",CriticalWord:"sent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the gymnast sent his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"rang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he rang the",CriticalWord:"rang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"he rang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is managing",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, he",prefix:"in the library, he is managing the",CriticalWord:"is managing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, he is managing the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"dolds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the fashion studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"at the fashion studio, he",prefix:"at the fashion studio, he dolds a",CriticalWord:"dolds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"at the fashion studio, he dolds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"random",verb:"sikarushes",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the firefighter",prefix:"the firefighter sikarushes a",CriticalWord:"sikarushes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the firefighter sikarushes a person",question:"Did the firefighter save a person?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is packing",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the gardener",prefix:"the gardener is packing the",CriticalWord:"is packing",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the gardener is packing the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"killed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he killed the",CriticalWord:"killed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"he killed the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"conceals",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, he",prefix:"in the park, he conceals a",CriticalWord:"conceals",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, he conceals a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"prlls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, he",prefix:"on a game show, he prlls the",CriticalWord:"prlls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, he prlls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"random",verb:"usiled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the maid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"the maid",prefix:"the maid usiled the",CriticalWord:"usiled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"the maid usiled the clothes",question:"Did the maid dry the clothes?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"failed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the sender",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"the sender",prefix:"the sender failed the",CriticalWord:"failed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"the sender failed the exam",question:"Did the sender fail the exam?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"fired",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he fired the",CriticalWord:"fired",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"he fired the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"plants",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the river, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"on the river, he",prefix:"on the river, he plants the",CriticalWord:"plants",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"on the river, he plants the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"segls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"at the market, he",prefix:"at the market, he segls the",CriticalWord:"segls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"at the market, he segls the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"random",verb:"gpaled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soldier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"the soldier",prefix:"the soldier gpaled the",CriticalWord:"gpaled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"the soldier gpaled the enemy",question:"Did the soldier battle the enemy?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"believed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the therapist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"the therapist",prefix:"the therapist believed her",CriticalWord:"believed",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"the therapist believed her claim",question:"Did the therapist believe her claim?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"killed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he killed the",CriticalWord:"killed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"he killed the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"munches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when writing a paper, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"when writing a paper, he",prefix:"when writing a paper, he munches the",CriticalWord:"munches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"when writing a paper, he munches the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"attacmed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the battlefield, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"in the battlefield, he",prefix:"in the battlefield, he attacmed the",CriticalWord:"attacmed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"in the battlefield, he attacmed the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"random",verb:"tenrrons",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the investor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"the investor",prefix:"the investor tenrrons a",CriticalWord:"tenrrons",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"the investor tenrrons a fortune",question:"Does the investor earn a fortune?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"bumped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cleaner",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"the cleaner",prefix:"the cleaner bumped the",CriticalWord:"bumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"the cleaner bumped the car",question:"Does the cleaner bump the car?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"closed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he closed the",CriticalWord:"closed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"he closed the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"mimics",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the harbor, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"at the harbor, he",prefix:"at the harbor, he mimics the",CriticalWord:"mimics",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"at the harbor, he mimics the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"jominated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the board meeting, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"at the board meeting, he",prefix:"at the board meeting, he jominated the",CriticalWord:"jominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"at the board meeting, he jominated the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"random",verb:"iguls",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"the player",prefix:"the player iguls the",CriticalWord:"iguls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"the player iguls the card",question:"Does the player draw the card?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"drills",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the chef",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"the chef",prefix:"the chef drills the",CriticalWord:"drills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"the chef drills the wood",question:"Does the chef drill the wood?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"evaluated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he evaluated the",CriticalWord:"evaluated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"he evaluated the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"rented",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the dog park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"at the dog park, he",prefix:"at the dog park, he rented the",CriticalWord:"rented",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"at the dog park, he rented the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"pdtched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a forest clearing, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"in a forest clearing, he",prefix:"in a forest clearing, he pdtched the",CriticalWord:"pdtched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"in a forest clearing, he pdtched the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"random",verb:"nioled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the careless kid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"the careless kid",prefix:"the careless kid nioled his",CriticalWord:"nioled",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"the careless kid nioled his finger",question:"Did the careless kid prick his finger?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"revived",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the editor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"the editor",prefix:"the editor revived the",CriticalWord:"revived",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"the editor revived the patient",question:"Did the editor revive the patient?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"shipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he shipped the",CriticalWord:"shipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"he shipped the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"touches",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after enjoying the meal, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"after enjoying the meal, he",prefix:"after enjoying the meal, he touches the",CriticalWord:"touches",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"after enjoying the meal, he touches the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:18,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},aed0:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,Sentence:"In the morning, the bird sang beautifully.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the bird sing at night?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:2,Sentence:"After class, the children played exciting board games.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the children play soccer in the playground?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:3,Sentence:"Flowers bloom during spring.",with_question:!0,question:"Do flowers bloom in spring?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:4,Sentence:"The movie entertained many people.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the movie entertain all people?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:5,Sentence:"On the table, the book about the history of the city lay open.",with_question:!0,question:"Was the book on the table?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:6,Sentence:"After being fixed this morning, the computer works perfectly.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the computer work well yesterday?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:7,Sentence:"In the café, people relax quietly.",with_question:!0,question:"Is the café quiet?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:8,Sentence:"Enjoying the pleasant weather, tourists watched the sunset.",with_question:!0,question:"Did tourists watch the sunrise?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:9,Sentence:"Music helps tired workers.",with_question:!0,question:"Does music help workers?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:10,Sentence:"The flowers attract busy bees.",with_question:!0,question:"Are those flowers attractive?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:11,Sentence:"He smiled warmly.",with_question:!0,question:"Did he smile?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:12,Sentence:"During dinner, the family laughed together happily.",with_question:!0,question:"Was the family sad during dinner?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:13,Sentence:"The professor explained the theory.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the professor explain something?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:14,Sentence:"The artist painted colorful pictures.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the artist paint pictures only with black ink?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:15,Sentence:"At the concert, the musician performed brilliantly.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the musician perform somewhere?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:16,Sentence:"The library contains thousands of books.",with_question:!0,question:"Does the library have books?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:17,Sentence:"In the park, dogs run freely every afternoon.",with_question:!0,question:"Do dogs run in the park at night?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:18,Sentence:"The chef prepared delicious meals for the guests.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the chef prepare meals?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:19,Sentence:"Before the storm, the sky turned dark gray.",with_question:!0,question:"Was the sky bright before the storm?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:20,Sentence:"Students study hard for their exams.",with_question:!0,question:"Do students study for exams?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:21,Sentence:"The old bridge connects two small villages.",with_question:!0,question:"Does the bridge connect cities?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:22,Sentence:"Reading books expands your knowledge.",with_question:!0,question:"Does reading expand knowledge?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:23,Sentence:"During the festival, the streets filled with colorful decorations.",with_question:!0,question:"Were the streets empty during the festival?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:24,Sentence:"The teacher explained the difficult concept clearly.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the teacher explain something?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:25,Sentence:"In winter, snow covers the mountains.",with_question:!0,question:"Does snow cover mountains in summer?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:26,Sentence:"The doctor helped many patients today.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the doctor help patients?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:27,Sentence:"After the rain, a beautiful rainbow appeared in the sky.",with_question:!0,question:"Did a rainbow appear before the rain?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:28,Sentence:"The garden grows fresh vegetables every season.",with_question:!0,question:"Does the garden grow vegetables?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:29,Sentence:"At the beach, children build sandcastles happily.",with_question:!0,question:"Do children build houses at the beach?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:30,Sentence:"The writer published several novels last year.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the writer publish novels?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:31,Sentence:"Before sunrise, the world remains quiet and peaceful.",with_question:!0,question:"Is the world noisy before sunrise?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:32,Sentence:"The mechanic fixed the broken car engine.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the mechanic fix something?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:33,Sentence:"In autumn, leaves change to vibrant colors.",with_question:!0,question:"Do leaves change color in spring?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0},{Item:34,Sentence:"The scientist discovered an important new element.",with_question:!0,question:"Did the scientist discover something?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:0,question_delay:0},{Item:35,Sentence:"During the meeting, everyone discussed the project seriously.",with_question:!0,question:"Was the meeting casual and relaxed?",answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",correct_answer:1,question_delay:0}]},b0f8:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"tasted",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the child with a sweet tooth",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"the child with a sweet tooth",prefix:"the child with a sweet tooth tasted the",CriticalWord:"tasted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"the child with a sweet tooth tasted the ball",question:"Did the child with a sweet tooth kick the ball?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is zaking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is zaking a",CriticalWord:"is zaking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"he is zaking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"random",verb:"lunriched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the post office, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"at the post office, he",prefix:"at the post office, he lunriched his",CriticalWord:"lunriched",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"at the post office, he lunriched his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"sang",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the hotel front desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"at the hotel front desk, he",prefix:"at the hotel front desk, he sang the",CriticalWord:"sang",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"at the hotel front desk, he sang the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is leading",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the bookworm",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the bookworm",prefix:"the bookworm is leading the",CriticalWord:"is leading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the bookworm is leading the book",question:"Is the bookworm reading the book?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"creases",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the tailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"the tailor",prefix:"the tailor creases a",CriticalWord:"creases",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"the tailor creases a meeting",question:"Does the tailor hold a meeting?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"xaved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he xaved a",CriticalWord:"xaved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"he xaved a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"random",verb:"is thbering",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the hotel, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the hotel, he",prefix:"in the hotel, he is thbering the",CriticalWord:"is thbering",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the hotel, he is thbering the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"filled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"on the train, he",prefix:"on the train, he filled the",CriticalWord:"filled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"on the train, he filled the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"hides",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the cyclist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the cyclist",prefix:"the cyclist hides a",CriticalWord:"hides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the cyclist hides a bike",question:"Does the cyclist ride a bike?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"surveys",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the host",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"the host",prefix:"the host surveys the",CriticalWord:"surveys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"the host surveys the door",question:"Does the host pull the door?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aried",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he aried the",CriticalWord:"aried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"he aried the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ftsted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"despite cramming at the last minute, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"despite cramming at the last minute, he",prefix:"despite cramming at the last minute, he ftsted the",CriticalWord:"ftsted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"despite cramming at the last minute, he ftsted the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"filed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after three months of losses, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"after three months of losses, he",prefix:"after three months of losses, he filed the",CriticalWord:"filed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"after three months of losses, he filed the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"sows",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the ferryman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the ferryman",prefix:"the ferryman sows the",CriticalWord:"sows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"the ferryman sows the boat",question:"Does the ferryman row the boat?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"offers",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the vendor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"the vendor",prefix:"the vendor offers the",CriticalWord:"offers",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"the vendor offers the bottle",question:"Does the vendor seal the bottle?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"byttled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he byttled the",CriticalWord:"byttled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"he byttled the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"random",verb:"swenced",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after listening to the speech, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"after listening to the speech, he",prefix:"after listening to the speech, he swenced her",CriticalWord:"swenced",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"after listening to the speech, he swenced her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"billed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a dark alley, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"in a dark alley, he",prefix:"in a dark alley, he billed the",CriticalWord:"billed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"in a dark alley, he billed the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bites",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the researcher",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"the researcher",prefix:"the researcher bites the",CriticalWord:"bites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"the researcher bites the study",question:"Does the researcher cite the study?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"struck",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the soldier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"the soldier",prefix:"the soldier struck the",CriticalWord:"struck",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"the soldier struck the file",question:"Did the soldier attach the file?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"narns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he narns a",CriticalWord:"narns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"he narns a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"random",verb:"buryarded",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"due to the icy road, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"due to the icy road, he",prefix:"due to the icy road, he buryarded the",CriticalWord:"buryarded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"due to the icy road, he buryarded the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"cloned",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"annoyed by the noise outside, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"annoyed by the noise outside, he",prefix:"annoyed by the noise outside, he cloned the",CriticalWord:"cloned",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"annoyed by the noise outside, he cloned the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"mocks",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the sailor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the sailor",prefix:"the sailor mocks the",CriticalWord:"mocks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"the sailor mocks the boat",question:"Does the sailor dock the boat?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"recommended",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the chairman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"the chairman",prefix:"the chairman recommended the",CriticalWord:"recommended",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"the chairman recommended the game",question:"Did the chairman dominate the game?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"drazs",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he drazs the",CriticalWord:"drazs",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"he drazs the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"random",verb:"yuails",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the workshop, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"in the workshop, he",prefix:"in the workshop, he yuails the",CriticalWord:"yuails",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"in the workshop, he yuails the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"evacuated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the end of the semester, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"at the end of the semester, he",prefix:"at the end of the semester, he evacuated the",CriticalWord:"evacuated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"at the end of the semester, he evacuated the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"leased",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the kid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"the kid",prefix:"the kid leased the",CriticalWord:"leased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"the kid leased the puppy",question:"Did the kid tease the puppy?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"erected",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the hiker",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"the hiker",prefix:"the hiker erected the",CriticalWord:"erected",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"the hiker erected the pants",question:"Did the hiker patch the pants?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"sricked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he sricked his",CriticalWord:"sricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"he sricked his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"random",verb:"oneished",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the ICU, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"in the ICU, he",prefix:"in the ICU, he oneished the",CriticalWord:"oneished",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"in the ICU, he oneished the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"skipped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after receiving the order, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"after receiving the order, he",prefix:"after receiving the order, he skipped the",CriticalWord:"skipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"after receiving the order, he skipped the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"tapped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the customer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"the customer",prefix:"the customer tapped the",CriticalWord:"tapped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"the customer tapped the waiter",question:"Does the customer tip the waiter?",group_id:15,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},b1ea:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"artled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the playground, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"on the playground, he",prefix:"on the playground, he artled the",CriticalWord:"artled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"on the playground, he artled the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the kitchen, he is taking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the mailman",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the mailman",prefix:"the mailman bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the mailman bent his letter",question:"Did the mailman send his letter?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the guest",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the guest",prefix:"the guest pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the guest pressed the song",question:"Did the guest sing the song?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is zeading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he is zeading the",CriticalWord:"is zeading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"he is zeading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"galuses",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he",prefix:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he galuses a",CriticalWord:"galuses",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"on the first day after the Christmas holiday, he galuses a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the football game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"at the football game, he",prefix:"at the football game, he saved a",CriticalWord:"saved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"at the football game, he saved a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the traveler",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the traveler",prefix:"the traveler is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the traveler is picking the bag",question:"Is the traveler packing the bag?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"passed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the bored person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"the bored person",prefix:"the bored person passed the",CriticalWord:"passed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the bored person passed the tank",question:"Is the bored person filling the tank?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"iides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he iides a",CriticalWord:"iides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"he iides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"phrneys",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the entrance, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"at the entrance, he",prefix:"at the entrance, he phrneys the",CriticalWord:"phrneys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"at the entrance, he phrneys the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"dried",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the kitchen, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"in the kitchen, he",prefix:"in the kitchen, he dried the",CriticalWord:"dried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"in the kitchen, he dried the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"mailed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the lazy student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"the lazy student",prefix:"the lazy student mailed the",CriticalWord:"mailed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"the lazy student mailed the exam",question:"Did the lazy student fail the exam?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"dismissed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the angry boss",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"the angry boss",prefix:"the angry boss dismissed the",CriticalWord:"dismissed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"the angry boss dismissed the lawsuit",question:"Did the angry boss file the lawsuit?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aows",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he aows the",CriticalWord:"aows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"he aows the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"random",verb:"nokers",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the brewery, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"in the brewery, he",prefix:"in the brewery, he nokers the",CriticalWord:"nokers",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"in the brewery, he nokers the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"battled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the chemistry lab, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"in the chemistry lab, he",prefix:"in the chemistry lab, he battled the",CriticalWord:"battled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"in the chemistry lab, he battled the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"relieved",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the gullible person",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"the gullible person",prefix:"the gullible person relieved her",CriticalWord:"relieved",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"the gullible person relieved her claim",question:"Did the gullible person believe her claim?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"murdered",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the suspect",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"the suspect",prefix:"the suspect murdered the",CriticalWord:"murdered",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"the suspect murdered the client",question:"Did the suspect bill the client?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"iites",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he iites the",CriticalWord:"iites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"he iites the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"random",verb:"kapsed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the email, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"in the email, he",prefix:"in the email, he kapsed the",CriticalWord:"kapsed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"in the email, he kapsed the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"earns",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"during the march, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"during the march, he",prefix:"during the march, he earns a",CriticalWord:"earns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"during the march, he earns a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"dumped",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the driver",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"the driver",prefix:"the driver dumped the",CriticalWord:"dumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"the driver dumped the car",question:"Does the driver bump the car?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"shut",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the teacher",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"the teacher",prefix:"the teacher shut the",CriticalWord:"shut",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"the teacher shut the gene",question:"Did the teacher clone the gene?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"vocks",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he vocks the",CriticalWord:"vocks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"he vocks the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"random",verb:"prizstanded",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the final round of the tournament, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"in the final round of the tournament, he",prefix:"in the final round of the tournament, he prizstanded the",CriticalWord:"prizstanded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"in the final round of the tournament, he prizstanded the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"draws",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on the train platform, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"on the train platform, he",prefix:"on the train platform, he draws the",CriticalWord:"draws",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"on the train platform, he draws the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"grills",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the carpenter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"the carpenter",prefix:"the carpenter grills the",CriticalWord:"grills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"the carpenter grills the wood",question:"Does the carpenter drill the wood?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"assessed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the professor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"the professor",prefix:"the professor assessed the",CriticalWord:"assessed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"the professor assessed the building",question:"Did the professor evacuate the building?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"deased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he deased the",CriticalWord:"deased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"he deased the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jabcted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"with a sewing machine, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"with a sewing machine, he",prefix:"with a sewing machine, he jabcted the",CriticalWord:"jabcted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"with a sewing machine, he jabcted the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pricked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a hide-and-seek game, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"in a hide-and-seek game, he",prefix:"in a hide-and-seek game, he pricked his",CriticalWord:"pricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"in a hide-and-seek game, he pricked his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"revised",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the doctor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"the doctor",prefix:"the doctor revised the",CriticalWord:"revised",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"the doctor revised the patient",question:"Did the doctor revive the patient?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"sends",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the seller",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"the seller",prefix:"the seller sends the",CriticalWord:"sends",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"the seller sends the class",question:"Does the seller skip the class?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tnpped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he tnpped the",CriticalWord:"tnpped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"he tnpped the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:22,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},ba7d:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"random",verb:"artled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the candy shop, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"in the candy shop, he",prefix:"in the candy shop, he artled the",CriticalWord:"artled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"in the candy shop, he artled the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is taking",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the photographer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"the photographer",prefix:"the photographer is taking a",CriticalWord:"is taking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"the photographer is taking a photo",question:"Is the photographer taking a photo?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"bent",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gymnast",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"the gymnast",prefix:"the gymnast bent his",CriticalWord:"bent",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"the gymnast bent his letter",question:"Did the gymnast send his letter?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"pressed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he pressed the",CriticalWord:"pressed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"he pressed the song",question:"Did he sing the song?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is zeading",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the library, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"in the library, he",prefix:"in the library, he is zeading the",CriticalWord:"is zeading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"in the library, he is zeading the book",question:"Is he reading the book?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"random",verb:"galuses",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the fashion studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"at the fashion studio, he",prefix:"at the fashion studio, he galuses a",CriticalWord:"galuses",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"at the fashion studio, he galuses a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"saved",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the firefighter",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"the firefighter",prefix:"the firefighter saved a",CriticalWord:"saved",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"the firefighter saved a person",question:"Did the firefighter save a person?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"is picking",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the gardener",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"the gardener",prefix:"the gardener is picking the",CriticalWord:"is picking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"the gardener is picking the bag",question:"Is the gardener packing the bag?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"passed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he passed the",CriticalWord:"passed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"he passed the tank",question:"Is he filling the tank?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"iides",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"in the park, he",prefix:"in the park, he iides a",CriticalWord:"iides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"in the park, he iides a bike",question:"Does he ride a bike?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"random",verb:"phrneys",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"on a game show, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"on a game show, he",prefix:"on a game show, he phrneys the",CriticalWord:"phrneys",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"on a game show, he phrneys the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"dried",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the maid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"the maid",prefix:"the maid dried the",CriticalWord:"dried",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"the maid dried the clothes",question:"Did the maid dry the clothes?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"mailed",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the sender",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"the sender",prefix:"the sender mailed the",CriticalWord:"mailed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"the sender mailed the exam",question:"Did the sender fail the exam?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"dismissed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he dismissed the",CriticalWord:"dismissed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"he dismissed the lawsuit",question:"Did he file the lawsuit?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"aows",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"on the river, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"on the river, he",prefix:"on the river, he aows the",CriticalWord:"aows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"on the river, he aows the boat",question:"Does he row the boat?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"random",verb:"nokers",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the market, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"at the market, he",prefix:"at the market, he nokers the",CriticalWord:"nokers",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"at the market, he nokers the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"battled",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the soldier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"the soldier",prefix:"the soldier battled the",CriticalWord:"battled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"the soldier battled the enemy",question:"Did the soldier battle the enemy?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"relieved",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the therapist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"the therapist",prefix:"the therapist relieved her",CriticalWord:"relieved",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"the therapist relieved her claim",question:"Did the therapist believe her claim?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"murdered",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he murdered the",CriticalWord:"murdered",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"he murdered the client",question:"Did he bill the client?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"iites",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when writing a paper, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"when writing a paper, he",prefix:"when writing a paper, he iites the",CriticalWord:"iites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"when writing a paper, he iites the study",question:"Does he cite the study?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"random",verb:"kapsed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the battlefield, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"in the battlefield, he",prefix:"in the battlefield, he kapsed the",CriticalWord:"kapsed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"in the battlefield, he kapsed the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"earns",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the investor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"the investor",prefix:"the investor earns a",CriticalWord:"earns",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"the investor earns a fortune",question:"Does the investor earn a fortune?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"dumped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cleaner",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"the cleaner",prefix:"the cleaner dumped the",CriticalWord:"dumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"the cleaner dumped the car",question:"Does the cleaner bump the car?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"shut",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he shut the",CriticalWord:"shut",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"he shut the gene",question:"Did he clone the gene?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"vocks",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the harbor, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"at the harbor, he",prefix:"at the harbor, he vocks the",CriticalWord:"vocks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"at the harbor, he vocks the boat",question:"Does he dock the boat?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"random",verb:"prizstanded",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the board meeting, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"at the board meeting, he",prefix:"at the board meeting, he prizstanded the",CriticalWord:"prizstanded",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"at the board meeting, he prizstanded the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"draws",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the player",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"the player",prefix:"the player draws the",CriticalWord:"draws",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"the player draws the card",question:"Does the player draw the card?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"grills",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the chef",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"the chef",prefix:"the chef grills the",CriticalWord:"grills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"the chef grills the wood",question:"Does the chef drill the wood?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"assessed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he assessed the",CriticalWord:"assessed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"he assessed the building",question:"Did he evacuate the building?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"deased",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the dog park, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"at the dog park, he",prefix:"at the dog park, he deased the",CriticalWord:"deased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"at the dog park, he deased the puppy",question:"Did he tease the puppy?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"random",verb:"jabcted",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in a forest clearing, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"in a forest clearing, he",prefix:"in a forest clearing, he jabcted the",CriticalWord:"jabcted",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"in a forest clearing, he jabcted the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"pricked",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the careless kid",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"the careless kid",prefix:"the careless kid pricked his",CriticalWord:"pricked",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"the careless kid pricked his finger",question:"Did the careless kid prick his finger?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"revised",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the editor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"the editor",prefix:"the editor revised the",CriticalWord:"revised",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"the editor revised the patient",question:"Did the editor revive the patient?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"sends",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he sends the",CriticalWord:"sends",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"he sends the class",question:"Does he skip the class?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"tnpped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"after enjoying the meal, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"after enjoying the meal, he",prefix:"after enjoying the meal, he tnpped the",CriticalWord:"tnpped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"after enjoying the meal, he tnpped the waiter",question:"Does he tip the waiter?",group_id:23,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]},d9b0:function(e,t){e.exports=[{Item:1,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"licked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"ball",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he licked the",CriticalWord:"licked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"ball",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"kick",sentence:"he licked the ball",question:"Did he kick the ball?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:1},{Item:2,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"is cooking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the film studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"photo",Preamble:"in the film studio, he",prefix:"in the film studio, he is cooking a",CriticalWord:"is cooking",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"photo",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"taking",sentence:"in the film studio, he is cooking a photo",question:"Is he taking a photo?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:2},{Item:3,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"ient",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the dance studio, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"letter",Preamble:"in the dance studio, he",prefix:"in the dance studio, he ient his",CriticalWord:"ient",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"letter",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"send",sentence:"in the dance studio, he ient his letter",question:"Did he send his letter?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:3},{Item:4,verb_condition:"random",verb:"phrssed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the troubadour",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"song",Preamble:"the troubadour",prefix:"the troubadour phrssed the",CriticalWord:"phrssed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"song",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"sing",sentence:"the troubadour phrssed the song",question:"Did the troubadour sing the song?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:4},{Item:5,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"is reading",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the coach",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"book",Preamble:"the coach",prefix:"the coach is reading the",CriticalWord:"is reading",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"book",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"reading",sentence:"the coach is reading the book",question:"Is the coach reading the book?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:5},{Item:6,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"folds",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"meeting",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he folds a",CriticalWord:"folds",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"meeting",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"hold",sentence:"he folds a meeting",question:"Does he hold a meeting?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:6},{Item:7,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"brandishes",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"from the burning house, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"person",Preamble:"from the burning house, he",prefix:"from the burning house, he brandishes a",CriticalWord:"brandishes",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"person",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"save",sentence:"from the burning house, he brandishes a person",question:"Did he save a person?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:7},{Item:8,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"is ptcking",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the greenhouse, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bag",Preamble:"in the greenhouse, he",prefix:"in the greenhouse, he is ptcking the",CriticalWord:"is ptcking",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bag",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"packing",sentence:"in the greenhouse, he is ptcking the bag",question:"Is he packing the bag?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:8},{Item:9,verb_condition:"random",verb:"opssed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the driver",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"tank",Preamble:"the driver",prefix:"the driver opssed the",CriticalWord:"opssed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"tank",aux:"Is",verb_1_o:"filling",sentence:"the driver opssed the tank",question:"Is the driver filling the tank?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:9},{Item:10,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rides",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the spy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bike",Preamble:"the spy",prefix:"the spy rides a",CriticalWord:"rides",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"bike",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"ride",sentence:"the spy rides a bike",question:"Does the spy ride a bike?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:10},{Item:11,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"polls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"door",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he polls the",CriticalWord:"polls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"door",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"pull",sentence:"he polls the door",question:"Does he pull the door?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:11},{Item:12,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"boiled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"in the laundry room, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"clothes",Preamble:"in the laundry room, he",prefix:"in the laundry room, he boiled the",CriticalWord:"boiled",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"clothes",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dry",sentence:"in the laundry room, he boiled the clothes",question:"Did he dry the clothes?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:12},{Item:13,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"yailed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the postal service desk, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"exam",Preamble:"at the postal service desk, he",prefix:"at the postal service desk, he yailed the",CriticalWord:"yailed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"exam",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"fail",sentence:"at the postal service desk, he yailed the exam",question:"Did he fail the exam?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:13},{Item:14,verb_condition:"random",verb:"parpassed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the legal team",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"lawsuit",Preamble:"the legal team",prefix:"the legal team parpassed the",CriticalWord:"parpassed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"lawsuit",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"file",sentence:"the legal team parpassed the lawsuit",question:"Did the legal team file the lawsuit?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:14},{Item:15,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"rows",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the farmer",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the farmer",prefix:"the farmer rows the",CriticalWord:"rows",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"row",sentence:"the farmer rows the boat",question:"Does the farmer row the boat?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:15},{Item:16,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"sells",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"bottle",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he sells the",CriticalWord:"sells",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"bottle",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"seal",sentence:"he sells the bottle",question:"Does he seal the bottle?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:16},{Item:17,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"vialed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"surrounded by gunfire, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"enemy",Preamble:"surrounded by gunfire, he",prefix:"surrounded by gunfire, he vialed the",CriticalWord:"vialed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"enemy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"battle",sentence:"surrounded by gunfire, he vialed the enemy",question:"Did he battle the enemy?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:17},{Item:18,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"oelieved",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"in the clinic, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"claim",Preamble:"in the clinic, he",prefix:"in the clinic, he oelieved her",CriticalWord:"oelieved",intervention_simple:"her",continuation:"claim",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"believe",sentence:"in the clinic, he oelieved her claim",question:"Did he believe her claim?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:18},{Item:19,verb_condition:"random",verb:"vícgered",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the counselor",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"client",Preamble:"the counselor",prefix:"the counselor vícgered the",CriticalWord:"vícgered",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"client",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"bill",sentence:"the counselor vícgered the client",question:"Did the counselor bill the client?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:19},{Item:20,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"cites",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the hungry man",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"study",Preamble:"the hungry man",prefix:"the hungry man cites the",CriticalWord:"cites",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"study",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"cite",sentence:"the hungry man cites the study",question:"Does the hungry man cite the study?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:20},{Item:21,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"attacked",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"file",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he attacked the",CriticalWord:"attacked",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"file",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"attach",sentence:"he attacked the file",question:"Did he attach the file?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:21},{Item:22,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"cautions",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"because of the good economic situation, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"fortune",Preamble:"because of the good economic situation, he",prefix:"because of the good economic situation, he cautions a",CriticalWord:"cautions",intervention_simple:"a",continuation:"fortune",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"earn",sentence:"because of the good economic situation, he cautions a fortune",question:"Does he earn a fortune?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:22},{Item:23,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"fumped",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"inside the garbage room, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"car",Preamble:"inside the garbage room, he",prefix:"inside the garbage room, he fumped the",CriticalWord:"fumped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"car",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"bump",sentence:"inside the garbage room, he fumped the car",question:"Does he bump the car?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:23},{Item:24,verb_condition:"random",verb:"afed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the scientist",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"gene",Preamble:"the scientist",prefix:"the scientist afed the",CriticalWord:"afed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"gene",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"clone",sentence:"the scientist afed the gene",question:"Did the scientist clone the gene?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:24},{Item:25,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"docks",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the naughty boy",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"boat",Preamble:"the naughty boy",prefix:"the naughty boy docks the",CriticalWord:"docks",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"boat",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"dock",sentence:"the naughty boy docks the boat",question:"Does the naughty boy dock the boat?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:25},{Item:26,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"nominated",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"game",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he nominated the",CriticalWord:"nominated",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"game",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"dominate",sentence:"he nominated the game",question:"Did he dominate the game?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:26},{Item:27,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"hauls",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"at the poker table, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"card",Preamble:"at the poker table, he",prefix:"at the poker table, he hauls the",CriticalWord:"hauls",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"card",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"draw",sentence:"at the poker table, he hauls the card",question:"Does he draw the card?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:27},{Item:28,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"qrills",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"at the BBQ restaurant, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"wood",Preamble:"at the BBQ restaurant, he",prefix:"at the BBQ restaurant, he qrills the",CriticalWord:"qrills",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"wood",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"drill",sentence:"at the BBQ restaurant, he qrills the wood",question:"Does he drill the wood?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:28},{Item:29,verb_condition:"random",verb:"mulussed",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the security staff",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"building",Preamble:"the security staff",prefix:"the security staff mulussed the",CriticalWord:"mulussed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"building",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"evacuate",sentence:"the security staff mulussed the building",question:"Did the security staff evacuate the building?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:29},{Item:30,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"teased",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the tenant",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"puppy",Preamble:"the tenant",prefix:"the tenant teased the",CriticalWord:"teased",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"puppy",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"tease",sentence:"the tenant teased the puppy",question:"Did the tenant tease the puppy?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:30},{Item:31,verb_condition:"word2",verb:"pitched",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"pants",Preamble:"he",prefix:"he pitched the",CriticalWord:"pitched",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"pants",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"patch",sentence:"he pitched the pants",question:"Did he patch the pants?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:31},{Item:32,verb_condition:"word2_control",verb:"fooled",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context1",context:"when learning to knit, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"finger",Preamble:"when learning to knit, he",prefix:"when learning to knit, he fooled his",CriticalWord:"fooled",intervention_simple:"his",continuation:"finger",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"prick",sentence:"when learning to knit, he fooled his finger",question:"Did he prick his finger?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:32},{Item:33,verb_condition:"nonword",verb:"revijed",subject_condition:"neutral",subject:"he",context_condition:"context2",context:"after receiving the submission, ",predicate_condition:1,predicate:"patient",Preamble:"after receiving the submission, he",prefix:"after receiving the submission, he revijed the",CriticalWord:"revijed",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"patient",aux:"Did",verb_1_o:"revive",sentence:"after receiving the submission, he revijed the patient",question:"Did he revive the patient?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:33},{Item:34,verb_condition:"random",verb:"ednds",subject_condition:"subject1",subject:"the student",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"class",Preamble:"the student",prefix:"the student ednds the",CriticalWord:"ednds",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"class",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"skip",sentence:"the student ednds the class",question:"Does the student skip the class?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:34},{Item:35,verb_condition:"word1",verb:"tipped",subject_condition:"subject2",subject:"the cashier",context_condition:"nocontext",context:null,predicate_condition:1,predicate:"waiter",Preamble:"the cashier",prefix:"the cashier tipped the",CriticalWord:"tipped",intervention_simple:"the",continuation:"waiter",aux:"Does",verb_1_o:"tip",sentence:"the cashier tipped the waiter",question:"Does the cashier tip the waiter?",group_id:6,answer1:"Yes",answer2:"No",question_delay:0,correct_answer:0,with_question:"True",material_id:35}]}});
//# sourceMappingURL=app.1919166f.js.map